There he is! Cut him off!
Stop in the name of…
Right there!
- Go!
He's over there! Get him!
- There he is.
- Don't let him get away!
After him!
Stop!
An Earthbender.
Hurry!
Come on!
Now! Now!
He went that way!
Get that to the Earth King.
They're going to start a war!
- There!
- Go now!
You're too late.
Your battle plans are already on their way
to the Earth Kingdom.
Good.
That means all eyes
will be on the Earth Kingdom.
All eyes but ours.
We'll be prepared for your attack.
When your king receives those plans,
he will redirect his forces
to your borders
and rally the support
of the other nations.
The Water Tribes
and the Air Nomads and the entire world
will turn their attention
to the Earthbenders.
You… you wanted us to know?
We aren't the real target.
My sights are set higher.
Much higher.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Because it is our time.
A masterful ruse, Your Highness.
But tactically,
the Airbenders are not the threat.
This isn't about the Airbenders.
This is about one who lives among them.
The only one
who could possibly stand in our way.
But the Avatar is yet to be revealed.
Which is why we have to kill them all.
Water.
Earth.
Fire.
Air.
For millennia,
the four nations have lived in harmony,
a peace made possible by the Avatar…
the one person with the ability
to master all four elements
and protect the delicate balance
between nations.
When one Avatar dies,
their spirit is reborn into a new body
in an eternal cycle.
Since the death of the last Avatar,
the new incarnation has yet to emerge.
And so Fire Lord Sozin,
the ruthless leader of the Fire Nation,
believes this is his moment
to launch a merciless campaign
to conquer the world.
His first step is
to eliminate the one person
who could stand in his way.
The next master of all four elements,
an Airbender who may not be ready
for the responsibility of becoming
the Avatar.
Aang!
- Hey, look!
- Yeah!
Wow!
Who else?
Whoa!
Show-off.
- What? I was just enjoying the view.
- Ha.
Monk Tsutop was looking for you.
You skipped training again!
It's all the same drills.
You know I already know all this stuff.
Aang.
You may be more advanced than the others,
but there's much you have to learn.
And believe it or not,
there may come a day when you wish
you'd spent more time with your teachers.
Now, you and the other students
better go help set up
for the Great Comet Festival.
Still a lot of work to be done
before the Air Nomads
from the other temples arrive.
How many are coming?
Wait. What's that sound?
Look! Up there!
Look at all of them.
Wow! There's so many!
Look at all of them!
All of them.
Come on, Aang! They're right up there!
Wait up!
Did you tell him?
- It wasn't the right time.
- The right time?
We don't have the luxury
of waiting for the right time.
We need to go talk to the council now.
Aang has always been a prodigy.
The youngest Airbender in history
to receive the markings of a master.
But he is only 12.
We can't ask this of him.
Fire Lord Sozin
is planning to attack the Earth Kingdom.
The Water Tribes are already sending
the warriors to aid the Earthbenders,
and we need to help them as well.
And we need the Avatar.
Yes, Aang is powerful,
but there's much he still needs to learn
about responsibility,
expectations,
sacrifice.
Most of all, he needs to know who he is.
If we send him away
before he learns these things,
he could fail to be
everything we need him to be.
And he and the world
might never recover from that.
The role of the Avatar
is a heavy responsibility,
not meant for a child.
But it is not our place
to choose who bears that burden,
and I fear you've grown too close to Aang
to see that, Brother Gyatso.
Aang must leave immediately
to begin training
in the other bending disciplines,
and we can only hope
that it is not too late for him
to make a difference.
Are comet festivals always this much work?
Well, the last one was
a hundred years ago,
and believe it or not,
I'm actually not old enough
to have seen that.
Could have fooled me.
Remember the last time I brought you here?
Sure. When I got my tattoos.
Most receive their markings
in the main hall,
but I wanted you to receive yours
in the presence of Yangchen,
the last Air Nomad to be the Avatar.
When she died, the next Avatar was born
into the following nation
in the eternal cycle,
so after Yangchen's death
came Kuruk of the Water Tribes,
then Kyoshi of the Earth Kingdom…
And then Roku in the Fire Nation.
Which means the next Avatar
will once again be an Airbender.
Her spirit echoes in one of us.
Aang, you have always been special.
The most talented Airbender
I have ever known.
I never asked to be special.
But you are.
Aang,
you are the Avatar.
The Fire Nation
has embarked on a dark path.
Their actions threaten
to throw the world out of balance.
Only the Avatar, the one person
who can master all four elements,
can save the world.
The world needs the Avatar.
The world needs you, Aang.
You're to leave right away so you can
begin training in the other disciplines.
Right away?
Leave my friends? Leave home? Leave you?
Now, this
would be a huge burden for anyone,
but you're not just anyone, Aang.
You're strong
and kind
and generous.
Remember that.
Always remember who you are
because I can't imagine a better person
to have been given this power.
I don't want… the power.
Which is why you will make a great Avatar.
Why do I have to be different?
Can't I just
keep pretending that I'm your friend?
You are my friend.
You… will always be my friend.
Hey, Appa.
Couldn't sleep either, huh?
Gyatso says I'm supposed to be the Avatar.
Me.
Monks don't even trust me
to feed the baby bison,
and I'm supposed to save the world?
He said I need to remember who I am.
But I know who I am.
I like to play airball
and eat banana cakes
and goof off with my friends.
That's who I am,
not someone who can stop the Fire Nation.
Not someone who can stop a war.
The other kids always say I'm lucky
because of the things I could do,
but I'd trade places with any of them.
I don't wanna leave.
I don't want the responsibility.
I'm scared of my power.
I'm scared of being alone!
I'm scared.
You're right.
I just need to go up
where things always make more sense.
At least for now.
Yip, yip!
Remember,
no survivors.
Brothers and sisters, we're under attack!
Yah!
- What's going on?
- Come with me, quickly!
Where's Aang?
Aang!
Quickly, move along.
It's getting kind of rough, Appa.
Maybe we should head back home?
That's it.
Stay quiet. You'll be safe in there.
Right into the corner.
Stay down.
It's okay, Appa!
Steady!
Oh!
You may have prevailed on another night.
But not when we have
the power of the comet!
Ah!
Come on!
All right, listen up.
We've been manning the wall
in three-hour shifts,
but it seems some of you can't be trusted
to stay at your posts.
So from now on,
two people at all times,
meaning twice as many shifts.
Is there a problem?
Didn't think so.
Okay, back to your duties.
Come on, let's go.
Where are we going?
The fishing boats came back empty.
Just proves if you want something
done right, gotta do it yourself.
They don't appreciate
your incredible leadership skills.
That's right. They don't realize it.
Very funny.
Katara!
So where were you before?
You were waterbending again, weren't you?
Don't worry. No one could see me.
Not that it matters.
Of course it matters. If the Fire Nation
finds out you're a Waterbender--
No one from the Fire Nation
has approached the village in years.
Besides, there's nothing to see.
An otter penguin
could bend more water than I could.
It's probably for the best.
You should be helping out more
around the village anyway.
Not everything
is about preparing to fight.
-We're at war.
-Waterbending is what built our culture.
Our way of life.
Keeping it alive is our duty.
-Keeping ourselves alive is our duty.
-I know that.
-And if Dad were here--
-But he's not here! I am!
Katara.
Katara. Sulk later, paddle now.
Good job.
I'm not doing this.
Sokka!
You okay?
Oh no. No, no, that's not good.
What is that?
Huh, weird.
We need to get that canoe,
or we're gonna end up as fish food,
which would be ironic.
Maybe I could float over on some ice?
Uh, Katara?
Finally.
Where did he come from?
I don't know.
Oh! Nice. Nice. We're not gonna die.
Come on. Let's go home.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! What are you doing?
You're not thinking of leaving him?
Katara, a strange, glowy iceberg
just exploded and left behind
a mysterious little bald person.
What part of that makes you think,
"Great, let's bring him home"?
Sokka, he's just a kid.
We can't just leave him out here.
I don't like this, but why listen to me?
I'm just responsible
for the safety of the village.
-He looks dead.
-What's that mark on his head?
Let me take a look.
It can't be.
What is it, Gran Gran?
This is an Airbender.
It's impossible.
Airbenders don't exist anymore.
Well, we won't get any answers
until he wakes up.
We need to let him rest.
Come on.
The only settlement in that area
is Water Tribe Village
in the South Pole territory.
That's where we have to go.
-Where you think we'll find the Avatar?
-Yes.
Because of the light?
You think I'm imagining things?
Sometimes, light beams are nothing more
than celestial glimmers in the winter sky.
For three years,
I've chased down every hint, every rumor,
every whisper of the Avatar,
and I'll keep doing it
for another three years if I have to.
Prince Zuko,
I don't think your father would want you--
My father has banished me
until I find the Avatar,
and that's exactly what I'll do.
All I'm saying is,
it's hard to see you get your hopes up
every time you see a…
a sign.
It'll all be worth it
once I return home in glory
to take my place
as the rightful heir to the Fire Lord.
Perhaps it's time to consider
that the throne isn't everything.
It may not have been for you.
But for me…
it's my destiny.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on!
Got you!
Gotcha!
Hey, get away from him!
What are you thinking?
Have you forgotten your training?
What'd I say about keeping your guard up?
He could be the enemy.
The enemy?
I'm not the enemy.
Then who are you?
I'm Aang.
Where am I?
-How'd I get here?
-You tell me.
Wait.
Appa?
Appa!
Where's Appa?
Sokka!
Have you seen him?
Yeah.
That's not strange at all.
- This is unbelievable.
- Appa!
He is an Airbender.
Have you seen Appa?
My sky bison.
Six legs, horns, brown arrows?
Sky bison.
-Sky bison!
-Repeating it doesn't help.
- Whoa!
- What is that thing?
Appa!
Sky bison.
You say you went down in the storm?
It came upon us suddenly.
The weather went crazy
just after I left home.
The Southern Air Temple.
Where the Air Nomads live.
Well, not all the Air Nomads,
but most of them had just arrived
for the Great Comet Festival.
The Great Comet Festival.
Gran Gran?
Water, earth, fire, air.
Long ago, the four nations
lived together in harmony.
Then everything changed
when the Fire Nation attacked.
Only the Avatar,
master of all four elements,
could stop them.
But when the world needed him most,
he vanished.
And so the Fire Nation
marched and laid waste,
plunging us into a time of darkness.
Everyone in the village knows this story,
but you don't, do you, young man?
Just as you don't know that Airbenders
haven't been seen in generations
and that the Southern Air Temple
was the first to fall,
because you've been trapped
in that ice this whole time.
The last time that the Great Comet
was seen in the sky
was 100 years ago.
He may seem like just a boy,
but he's much more.
He is the last Airbender.
Of all the places to drag our asses to,
he picks the coldest spot in the world.
How come his omens never take us
somewhere with hot springs, huh?
-Something you wanna say, Lieutenant Jee?
-No, sir.
Let me make something clear.
Our mission is vital
to the future of the Fire Nation,
and so we will find the Avatar.
We will prove ourselves worthy,
and we will see
our homes and families again…
or we will die trying.
Are you okay?
A hundred years.
All my friends,
everyone I know…
they're all gone.
Um, I'm sorry.
Believe me, I know how hard it is
to lose the people you love.
When I was little,
I didn't really understand the war
until the night the Firebenders came.
They destroyed everything in their path.
Everything.
Everyone.
Afterwards, our father set out
with the other warriors
to hunt down the Firebenders.
That was three years ago,
and we haven't seen him since.
He had left Sokka in charge
when he just turned 13.
I guess he had to grow up fast.
We all did.
We're never really ready
until we have to be.
They were part of the Fire Nation's
first attacks on the Water Tribe.
The Firebenders were ruthless.
Since then, the Fire Nation
has conquered most of the world.
But the Waterbenders
are still fighting back,
especially in the North.
And the Earth Kingdom
is still holding strong.
We hope.
I had friends in the Fire Nation.
I used to visit them.
No one visits other nations now.
We're only friends with our own kind.
Good. Your skills have never been sharper.
I need to be at my best
when I face the world's ultimate warrior.
They say Avatar Kyoshi took down
an entire squadron
of Earth Kingdom soldiers single-handedly.
Well, you've certainly prepared enough.
Now, how about a nice cup of jasmine tea?
Say we find the Avatar,
and you're able to defeat him,
a mission
your father believed to be impossible.
And so your return home may be…
unexpected.
You're wrong.
No one comes here.
It's quiet and hidden.
You're a Waterbender!
Barely. I'm trying to get better,
but I'm the only Waterbender left
in the Southern Tribe.
Sokka doesn't like it when I practice
because he's worried
that the Fire Nation will find out and…
And what?
There's a reason I'm the only Waterbender
left in the village.
They've killed all the others.
Sokka just doesn't understand.
I'm a warrior. I should be able
to do more for our people.
The monks told me
bending is about energy and balance.
By feeling the energy around you,
you can find balance.
By finding balance,
you can feel the energy.
Nice!
I wasn't even really trying.
That's good. You just have to let go.
Katara?
Sokka! Sokka, the Fire Nation. They're--
I know. We spotted them.
Get to your posts now!
-Sokka, the racks--
-Get them loaded.
I don't understand. Why are they here?
After all this time,
what could they possibly want?
Him.
He's more than the last Airbender.
Aren't you?
You are the Avatar.
Aang?
I knew he was hiding something.
When the world needed the Avatar the most,
he vanished because he's a coward.
He ran, and people died.
Sokka, they've landed.
You need to go hide.
-Sokka, I wanna--
-Katara, now.
Come on. We need to get somewhere safe.
I am Prince Zuko.
Firstborn son of Fire Lord Ozai.
We have no desire to take your homes.
We merely seek someone
who does not belong here.
Someone who is not one of you.
Turn him over now,
or I'll burn this place to the ground.
-Where is he?
-Sokka, you can't give him to them--
-He doesn't belong here.
-It's wrong. You know that!
What I know
is Dad told me to protect the village.
Yes, but remember what Mom told us too.
She said that we have to protect those
who can't protect themselves.
He's lost everything he knows.
-Sokka, don't you see? He's the Avatar!
-And he lied to us about it!
I know how hard
this responsibility has been for you,
but there's more to being a leader
than just catching fish.
You have to give people
something to live for.
That's what the Avatar is. He's hope.
And we need that
just as much as we need food and shelter.
I know I do.
I am Sokka.
Son of Hakoda.
Lord of, uh,
Snow and Ice.
On behalf
of the Water Tribe Village of Wolf Cove,
I demand that you leave immediately!
If this is the path you've chosen,
then so be it.
Let's settle this between us!
Leader to leader. You really need an army?
I thought you Firebenders had some guts.
Don't fall for it.
We overpower them. It's no contest.
Well, where's the glory in that?
I accept.
Who needs an army now?
Leave him alone!
Can't be.
Ah!
Enough games.
Burn the whole place to the ground.
No!
I'll go with you. Just leave them alone.
I'm the one you're looking for.
-Get him.
-Wait!
It's okay, Katara.
No one has ever fought for me before.
I think you're the bravest person
I've ever met.
We have to do something.
Sokka, we have to help him. Sokka!
Okay, listen up.
Reinforce the braces on the gate,
and don't fall behind on drills.
-I saw real sloppiness out there today.
-Drills?
And don't let the younger ones
push you around.
You gotta let 'em know who's in charge.
That's right.
You're in charge.
Now, let's go save that weird kid.
There are many who never imagined
this day would ever come, myself included.
Can I ask you something?
-Uh…
-Forgive me.
I'm Iroh, son of Fire Lord Azulon.
And of course.
Why did the Fire Nation start this war?
Ah.
Some people say it is within our nature
to expand and consume like fire itself.
Others believe
that true stability in this world
can only happen under our rule,
so the drive to conquer
is a drive for peace and unity.
But peace comes from respecting life,
not killing and destroying.
A noble sentiment, Avatar,
but in the end, for most of us,
it doesn't matter how this war started.
It only matters how it can end.
And the belief is that by capturing you,
the Fire Nation
can finally bring that about.
Is that what you believe?
I must leave, but I look forward to
many more conversations with you, Avatar.
In the meantime,
I'll have some jasmine tea sent to you.
It's quite soothing.
-It won't be easy to catch them.
-I know.
Hopefully, we can find a swift current.
Maybe draft off their wake.
Or
we could go another way.
You're not serious.
Katara, no!
There's no way you're getting me on that…
The Avatars.
Yes, sir, right away.
Stop!
Stop him!
Get him!
Open fire, now!
Ah!
Hey, kid!
Sokka!
Ah!
I can't believe
you guys came for me. Thank you.
It's time we showed those flameheads
they can't step on us.
The Firebenders aren't gonna give up.
They're gonna keep coming after you.
Which means we can't go home.
It would put everyone in danger.
So where do we go?
Gyatso.
Now, this would be
a huge burden for anyone,
but you're not just anyone, Aang.
You're strong
and kind and generous.
Remember that.
Always remember who you are.
Aang?
What's happening?
What is he doing?
Aang!
Come on!
Stop this!
Please!
Aang!
Aang,
I can't imagine a better person
to have been given this power.
You are my friend.
You will always be my friend.
So not to be rude,
but what was that?
I don't know.
There's so much I don't know.
The monks are gone, and I'm all alone.
You know,
the thing about losing everything
is that that's when you learn
how strong you really are.
It's when you learn to fight.
They made
the ultimate sacrifice for me.
I need to make sure
their deaths weren't in vain.
I need to follow through
on what they wanted me to do.
Complete my training
and master all the other bending skills
so I can bring balance back to the world.
Oh, is that all?
This was my home, and now it's gone.
It's only after
we've lost something
that we realize how much it means to us…
and how we'd do anything to get it back.
Anything.
I don't know where this will all lead,
and I don't know if I have what it takes,
but the one thing I do know is
I'm the Avatar,
and this is just the beginning.