Mbah Sarap,
you were caught and punished
for using black magic on humans.
There were too many victims
of your witchcraft.
I, as the Royal Chief, have decided,
to sentence you to death
for the sins that you have committed.
I was only trying to help people.
Liar! Don't trust her!
Please don't punish me!
Evil witch!
Soon you'll be dead.
Seek forgiveness from your victims
and repent to God!
When misery comes,
all of you will be looking for me.
When misery and hunger filled your lives…
I fed you and gave you wealth.
You were barren and worthless.
I gave you offspring.
I gave you all of those.
I gave you all of those!
Not from your God.
Be ready to die.
It's time for you to die.
Please let me go!
Release me from this punishment.
Or I will…
take all of your lives too.
Like wild animals!
Off with her head!
Can I get rice and egg?
Anything else? We have meat and fish.
Just an egg.
Okay, wait a minute.
-Here you go.
-How much?
With an egg, that'll be 8,500 rupiah.
Please take out the egg.
I'm short of money.
That's okay. You can have it.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Going somewhere, gorgeous?
You better pay up your father's debt.
I'll pay. But we have a deal.
I still have time.
My boss changed his mind.
You must pay it tonight
or you and your sister will be hookers.
Don't mess with us!
What are you looking at?
Three days.
Give me three days.
I'll pay off my father's debt.
You think I'm scared?
You cut him! He's bleeding!
You're dead, you hear me!
Enough.
I give you three days, or you're dead.
Let's go. Let's find a doctor.
Stop playing! Listen to me.
What is it?
You got my sister pregnant.
You told her to have an abortion.
This money isn't enough for that abortion!
You can take this!
-Bro.
-What do you want?
Where's Bagas?
Over there.
He refused to go to bed early.
He wanted to wait for you.
What happened to you, Lin?
I'm fine.
I'll take Bagas home now.
Lin, how is that fine?
-Bagas.
-You're still bleeding.
Let's go home.
I'm fine.
-Thanks, anyway.
-You're welcome.
You asshole! I'll kill you!
You'll die!
-Cowards!
-Stay away from Fitrah!
We don't need your money!
Stop it!
You're dirt-poor!
Alin.
Bagas, why are you awake?
Are you thirsty?
Going back to sleep?
I'm hungry.
You haven't eaten?
-I only have this rice.
-Yes, I want it!
Don't you want to use a plate?
You want some?
You can have it all.
Come here.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
What happened to your hands?
-They're fine. Put this on.
-Okay.
-Are you ready?
-Ready.
-Where are we off to?
-To the moon.
-Are you sure?
-I'm sure.
-Let's fly.
-Pull up and take off.
We're so high in the sky. Keep flying!
Get ready!
-Beautiful, isn't it?
-Yeah!
There are the moon and the stars.
So cool!
Bagas?
Yes?
I have to go to work, okay?
Will you be long?
Please pray for me, okay?
This is for you.
So, when you're home later,
you'll bring so much money.
Then we can fly together.
Cheer up, big sis!
Okay! Let's fly one more time.
One, two, we're flying!
Look at those beautiful moons and stars.
Yeah.
Lots of moons?
You're right! We only have lots of stars!
Alin…
Alin!
Come with me, Alin.
I died because of you!
Your mother died too.
I will keep torturing you!
Die!
You got somebody's daughter pregnant.
You gamble! You're in debt.
Causing trouble everywhere.
Time to work.
No more causing trouble. Focus!
You're the one who brought trouble!
You asked Alin to work with us!
-Lin, it's better if you think it over.
-I'm still going.
It's easy for you to say!
No. I'm not okay with it.
Who do you think you are?
Telling people around.
-I thought we had a deal.
-A deal?
You set us up!
You left your brother to Gani.
Then you screw him over.
-Let it go, Fit.
-What?
Where is the recording?
Where is it?
Give it to me!
-Fit!
-Answer me, now!
You said there are two choices. What? Two!
One.
I'm robing with you tonight,
-Two?
-Fit.
I will report you to the police.
I'll make it three and you'll die tonight.
You're crazy!
-She's somebody's daughter!
-So?
You're out of your mind! Bastard!
Lin, you can't go.
Apologizing won't be enough
for your issue with Fitrah.
Your friend won't dare to mess with me.
Who said that?
I know for sure.
We're "visiting" someone's home.
We're robbing them.
Surely that comes with risks.
Our objectives are justified.
We have no choice.
Zia's heart surgery can't wait.
You got a girl pregnant
and want an abortion.
Now you send her money monthly.
That's my business!
Are you ready to give up nursing school?
I know you're not bad guys.
That's why I leave Bagas with you, Gan.
I still have to go with you.
Deal with your girlfriend.
Lin, why don't I just lend you the money?
I have enough savings to help you.
My late mother told me this.
"Son, you must be a decisive, strong,
and tough person to handle the problems."
"Whatever happens,
rain or shine, don't give up."
You have that inside of you.
Let's go.
The runners are
approaching the final 100 meters.
Runner Zia Deliana from East Java
is leading followed by her rivals.
Will she be able to bring a gold medal
to her contingent?
Zia Deliana stumbles
and is trying hard to get back up
but she can't finish the race.
And South Sumatra league passed her
and got first place.
Followed by two runners from Jakarta,
Magie and Hana,
in second and third place.
Now we'll see how Zia Deliana is doing…
Are we going?
Just wait.
So, she really is coming with us?
Yes, she is.
Lin, this is Zia.
She's my friend from Malang.
Zi?
Alin.
She's pretty, Gan.
Prettier than your last crush.
What was her name?
That girl from Depok,
the mini mart cashier?
The one who looked like Ancol's monkey?
Ancol's monkey!
Crap!
Your mouth really has no filter.
Enough! Stop it.
What are you doing?
Are we going to "visit"?
What a sulky boy.
Yeah, a sulky little boy.
Listen to me carefully, Alin.
Fitrah
and Gani…
are like family to me.
So, if anything happens to my family
because of you…
Surely that comes with risks.
I needed this to ensure
that I can come with you.
Our objectives are justified.
Now, I don't need it.
I have no problem with any of you.
All I need is money.
Okay, she's my responsibility.
Is that the house? That's cool!
Guys.
I think somebody's in the house.
There is a car parked outside.
But it's supposed to be empty.
Well, Doddy was told by his insider
who worked there as maid for three months.
They said the family is out every Friday.
Doddy's insider took a day off too.
Hello, love!
-Morning!
-Ready to go in?
-Well, we are--
-Doddy, we arrived at the house,
but there is a car parked there.
It was confirmed that the house is empty.
Maybe they went on a trip without the car.
That's possible, right?
The point is they're gone…
-Doddy?
-Doddy.
Probably the signal.
Fit? What now?
We need to hold off on this.
-Then what do I do about Citra?
-That's your risk.
You know that.
You said Zia needs urgent surgery.
Fit, don't make her as an excuse.
The doctor said so!
-Not me!
-Blaming me?
Stop it!
-Zia!
-Zi!
It's fine.
You okay, Zi?
You said he's like a brother
from a different mother.
What family, you fool?
Come here.
If I ever see you both in a stupid fight,
I'm warning you!
Come on, chill it out.
-We're cool.
-Come on.
Shake hands.
Okay, sorry.
Be sincere.
-I'm sorry.
-Me too.
You guys are like kids.
-He goes nuts sometimes.
-Brothers should be loyal.
We wait until dark,
-then we decide if we'll be visiting.
-Zi!
Shit!
What's wrong with you?
Stop it.
Alin, what's wrong?
Sorry!
It's time.
We don't have much time.
This is yours.
Gani, this is your radio and flashlight.
What does Alin get?
She gets no radio and no flashlight,
so she has to be close to you.
Let's go!
Gan?
You two take the first floor.
I'll go upstairs.
Be back here in 30 minutes.
Alin, remember.
Take only the valuables
with large quantities.
Stuff they have lots of.
Take only what you need
so they don't realize it.
Don't be greedy.
Alin!
Bagas!
Lin?
Alin.
Alin!
What are you doing?
I saw Bagas here.
-That's impossible. Come on.
-I saw him right here.
It smells awful here, Lin.
Lin!
Lin.
Why are there bodies?
This is not right.
Help.
Please help me.
Zia!
Zia Deliana stumbles
and is trying hard to get back up…
Zia!
Yes, sorry!
Zi, get the car ready.
What's wrong?
Just get the car ready!
Gan.
We must help her, Lin.
But we don't know her.
We don't need to know, she needs us!
How did this happen to you?
Who are you?
They…
They wanted to sacrifice me.
They who?
Okay, wait.
Gan?
Don't leave me here.
Of course. Wait.
Slow down.
Come on, Lin!
Fitrah!
-Who's that?
-Don't ask.
-Where are you taking her?
-We need to get out.
What is that?
Lin?
What's wrong?
Gan?
I'm already at the gate.
Answer her.
Zi, we'll be out shortly.
Why are you answering? Where's Gani?
Fit, what's going on?
Hello? Gani? Fitrah!
What's going on?
Gani?
Shit!
Fit!
What the hell is going on?
You want us to all die here?
He's losing his mind.
-Fit, it's useless.
-Shut up.
Fit, don't do it!
You're crazy, Fit.
This is because of you.
-Come on, Fit.
-What do you mean "come on"?
We're going to die here.
We've "visited" many houses.
Why is this happening?
Pointing fingers
will not solve the problem.
Listen to me while I'm talking.
What is that?
-What are you doing?
-Give it to me.
Fit, come on. Stop it!
See? I was right.
Something is wrong with her!
I told you about the rules.
Why did you take all of this?
Looking for trouble?
-You're a thief!
-I'm not a thief!
I'm here because I have to be.
I need the money.
I hope this is the first and last time
I'm doing this.
I also don't want to live by stealing.
Enough.
We'll talk about it at home.
Now, we must find a way out.
Please don't go.
Fit, you and Alin
go find any way to get out.
Find out everything about this house.
Me? With Alin?
You're nuts.
Do you want to get out of here?
There's got to be a way.
But we need to find it.
Come on.
Gani is right.
Take this.
What's this?
To protect yourself.
Fit?
Thanks.
Okay.
A family tree.
Sukma Paratrika.
Friday Kliwon.
You can read this?
I went to school in Java.
Look at this!
This woman and Sukma
have the same Weton.
Friday Kliwon.
Sitarasmi Paratrika.
So what if it's the same weton?
All humans…
will die!
Zi?
Zia?
Fitrah!
Alin!
Bagas!
-Bagas!
-Alin!
You!
Who are you? Tell me!
What are you talking about?
Tell me who you are?
What did you do to my friends?
Answer me!
I've killed all of your friends!
What's really going on?
I am your friend.
-No, you're not.
-Now
it's time for you to die.
Gan!
Fitrah! Alin!
Give me back the knife.
I'll kill you!
Gan! Snap out of it!
Just give me the knife!
You've killed
all of my friends, my family!
Bastard!
I am your friend!
Your family, Zia!
You will never leave this house.
Open it!
Alin, where are you?
-Fit, where are you?
-In the yard, Zi.
Where are you?
I'm in the yard.
I'm here in the yard.
I'm right here.
You're not here, Fit.
Fitrah!
I'm right here.
I can't see you.
Who are you?
I'm Fitrah!
-Where is Fitrah?
-I am Fitrah.
Come with me.
Don't run, Zi!
Come with me!
We'll go to hell.
Forgive me…
I can't…
I can't take care of all of you.
My brothers…
Bagas?
What are you doing here?
DEADLY ACCIDENT IN TEBET
Alin!
Where are you going, Alin?
Don't run away!
I just saved all of you
from the effects of Median black magic.
This black magic
can drive the victims mad.
So, just calm down.
Try not to move.
Don't walk around. You might fall, stupid.
-Black magic.
-Slow down!
Median black magic.
-Don't mess with me, sir.
-That black magic…
uses worms as a medium
to induce hallucinations in the victim.
-Understand?
-Alin?
Now…
You need to explain to me
why did you let go that woman go?
Hey, you?
-Who are you?
-I'm nobody.
You are Mbah Sarap's grandson.
-I don't know who Mbah Sarap is.
-Then who?
Learning black magic?
I swear, I really don't know
anything about that stuff.
Then what are you doing here?
-We're just…
-Just what?
We just wanted to take money.
Like worshiping devil for money?
We're thieves.
Imbeciles!
Do you know…
the woman that you let go
is very dangerous.
Her power is more than
what you've already experienced.
Do you understand?
How would I know about that?
Something is different with you. Come on.
Well, stupid boy!
-Come on.
-Hey!
You're asking for trouble!
Please let him go.
Gan, are you okay?
Gan!
Gan, stop it!
Let me go, Lin!
Sir, please stop it!
We don't know who you are.
You could be trying to harm us!
If you don't know me, stop your nonsense!
Then tell us who you are!
All right, I'll tell you.
I am…
Urip Mahesworo.
A noble descendant
of the kingdom in the past.
Twenty years ago,
I was given the task to hunt down
those evildoers who practiced black magic.
Twenty-two hours ago,
I came to this house,
to end the Prewangan Heritage
of Mbah Sarap.
You know, we've experienced
lots of weird things here.
So, it makes sense we don't trust you.
Okay.
What are you doing to her?
I brought you here
to see how it all started.
No need to talk.
Now you're on Java Island in the past.
That one was…
the most powerful shaman at that time.
Her name is Mbah Sarap.
Sitarasmi Paratrika.
She gets the power from God
to create a supernatural entity
called "Khodam."
We called them Prewangan.
Mbah Sarap's Prewangan is called Wrejit.
Nobody can kill me.
Me and Wrejit will live forever.
A hundred years of her curse awaits,
until the next generation
who is born on the same day as hers
with the name Sukma.
Sukma Paratrika. Friday Kliwon.
This woman shares the same Weton as Sukma.
The woman you helped.
Come on, Lin!
Smart?
And that curse…
can only be broken
by the Keris Sirno Peteng.
I may die today.
But Wrejit will find
the chosen one from my descendants.
They will avenge my death.
All humans will die!
That's why
I came to this house,
to end the Wrejit's inheritance ritual
from passing to Sukma.
Stop all of this!
Who are you?
Urip Mahesworo.
So, you're the one to
hunt down and kill us.
Mom?
Before I find Sirno Peteng,
I must fight them.
The choices are to kill or be killed.
Thankfully, God answered my prayers.
I've weakened Sukma temporarily.
Until you came and ruined everything.
We absolutely…
had no intention of ruining your plans.
Me, Alin, and…
Where's Fitrah, Lin?
Sir, Fitrah is my friend.
Please help us find him.
Sir?
We have to find Keris Sirno Peteng.
The kris was lost 200 years ago.
However, I sense
a strong Batulangit energy here.
Mbah Sarap's children built this house,
to easily locate Sirno Peteng
and then cast it into the South Sea.
-So, the Keris?
-I think it can been found.
Because I sense
the energy is very strong there.
I feel coldness
coming from your friend's body,
and he's on the brink of death.
Say whatever you need
to say to him before…
-Urip!
-…it's too late.
There is a way.
We can go down there.
Look, there are stairs. We go down there.
Yes.
We have to find Sirno Peteng quickly
to stop Sukma.
So we can help your friend.
Lin, what's wrong?
I don't know either.
-Wait here, let me and Urip go.
-No, I'm coming.
Okay.
Be careful.
Lin?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Okay.
I think we need something to go in there.
I've been here before.
No way, Lin.
I've dreamed about this place.
Who are you exactly?
I am Gani.
Gani.
Impossible for Alin
to dream about this place.
What is this place?
Where are we?
Where's Alin?
Stop… Stop for a while…
Gravitate…
Kidung Semar.
The spell to ward off bad luck.
When it gravitates…
The spell against evil.
The spell of knights,
against the wrathful, to uphold the truth.
Alin?
What's wrong?
With evil in the mind
And evil in the feet
Evil in the feathers
Lies within the shoulders
Are anguish fueled
By rage and greed
Unseen by the naked eyes
Come back…
To the beginning
Sirno Peteng.
A straight kris
that signifies the heart's integrity,
courage,
and strength.
Lies within is…
Prewangan Garuda.
I ask your permission.
Don't…
Don't open it!
Where is that kris?
Tell me!
Or I will kill all of you!
Hey, Jebuk Arum,
the one called Menyan Kreges,
following the way Menyan smoke blows
up in the dark clouds,
fly high to the seventh sky,
buried deep to the earth's seventh layer,
enter the souls of the mystical ancestors!
Run!
In the name of the Almighty God,
ruler of the world,
the commander of all beings in the world,
free us from evil.
Let all the evildoers
return to the condemned hell.
May they all burst into bits.
By the power of the Almighty God.
Alin!
Zia.
Your life and death are in my hands.
Oh, Bethari Durgo,
ruler of Setragondomayit,
I sent unto you my spells,
my magical spells,
to possess the corpses.
Delivered by the haunting
demons and djinns
carrying with them the chant of my spells.
Powerful spells that touch everything.
Oh, wind with mighty power.
Bring to life the wind,
bring to life the words I spoke.
Life being a living word.
Oh, you, named with powers.
Come to life. Come to life.
Be alive!
Let's go!
Come on!
Lin.
Go ahead and go home first, Lin.
No. Let's go together, Gan.
-Fitrah. I must find him.
-You're going to die, Gan.
Urip said that you…
There's a drawer in my room.
I have some savings,
take it for you and Bagas.
-No, Gani.
-Please, take it.
Gan.
Lin. Our lives are in God's hands.
Not in Urip's hands.
-Gan.
-Go home now.
-Gani!
-Go home!
-No.
-Bagas is waiting.
Gani! Gani!
Gani!
Don't worry, Zi.
I won't leave you alone here.
Okay? Come on.
Family is loyal.
Let's find Fitrah now, Zi.
Gani!
We were destined
to share life and death.
Hey, Jebuk Arum,
the one called Menyan Kreges,
following the way Menyan smoke blows
up in the dark clouds,
fly high to the seventh sky,
buried deep to the earth's seventh layer.
Enter the souls of the mystical ancestors.
Enter… enter… enter.
Enter like the kris into its sheath.
Enter the souls into the flesh.
Whatever happens, come rain, come shine,
you don't give up.
It's time for you to die.
No. You'll die!
It's all right, Lin.
It's all right.
Such a weak mortal!
Can only cry for those tormented souls.
You all think death is the end…
of everything.
But death is my resurrection.
Watch me.
I'll show you the curse of Mbah Sarap!
Evil kid!
You killed your mother and father.
Maybe your brother is dead.
You left him alone, Alin!
Come join me in hell, Alin!
How dare you disobey me?
You're not my father.
I warned you.
All descendants of Mbah Sarap will be--
Shut up!
Gani?
Bagas.
Where is Gani?
Come on.
Hey!
Where are you going, gorgeous?
-Bagas, wait here.
-Okay.
Okay.
Hey.
Your father's debt is settled,
but you and I have unfinished business.
Let's go to a hotel.
Don't play hard to get,
or your brother will--
You want to fight me?
No way.
Boss, hey. Boss!
Sirno Peteng is born
to carry out noble tasks.
So you can't use it as you please.
Your aura exudes anger.
That means…
Sirno Peteng asked you
to clean the heirloom.
Just as your ancestors did.
Take good care of it.
Because it chose you.
You will draw strength from it.
As you also will…
make sacrifices for it.
Accept it sincerely.
Alin Wihanggamapati.