Are you gonna come in?
Or you gonna
stand there and drool?
You've got a mouth on you.
'What else is it good for?'
Why don't you come in
and you'll find out?
So what's your name, pretty?
Call me whatever you like.
I'm yours for tonight.
Courtesy of Santiago.
Since you look
good enough to eat,
I think I can call you...
...Candy.
What makes you think I'm sweet?
Now, why don't you
show it to me.
Wow.
Whatever you say, beauty.
Like a baby's arm
holding an apple, huh?
About big enough for the birds,
I reckon.
What the...
Just like cocks, power comes in
all different shapes and sizes.
You name it.
Sex, money, class, politics.
Or just the sheer will
to put the other man down
and leave 'em bleeding
on the floor.
But power
is nothing without respect.
If they don't respect you,
sooner or later some cunt
is gonna come along and take
that power away from you.
You!
Fucking kill him.
So this is me. Name's Scarlett.
London girl,
through and through.
The big bastard is Nacho,
but don't lose
any sleep over him,
he totally has it coming.
You're not real.
This feel real enough?
Oh, you dirty fucker.
Oh, hello.
Oh, no.
As you can probably tell
I've come
a long way from Peckham.
But I ain't done anything
to be ashamed of.
Well...
Fuck sake!
Not much anyway.
Actually hang on a minute. I'm
getting way ahead of myself.
To really understand
where this all started
we have to go back a bit.
Back to when I met the man
who changed everything.
No, not him.
That's just a mark.
And not him either.
That's Adam.
Think of him like
Fagin to me Artful Dodger.
Wherever I could pinch, he took
his cut and watched my back.
Now, that's my bestie,
Michelle.
Alright, babe, let's go to work.
If we saw an opportunity
we took it.
Back then I had
fuck all to lose.
No, I'm talking about the other
bloke in the background
who I didn't even see coming.
Yeah.
Okay.
Was that Victor?
We're all set. Charlie takes
delivery on Friday.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
Let's not ruin the moment.
I've been watching you work.
You got some nice moves.
- What is this, a bust?
- No.
Cops don't cut the hands
off the people
they catch stealing from them.
- I'm just kidding.
- So how's about you let me go?
How's about I don't?
Listen, my boyfriend's
over there
and you do not want
to mess with him.
So do yourself a favor
and piss off.
You do have a sting
in your tail, don't you?
Yeah, that's right.
So sling your hook.
- He's not your boyfriend
- Oh, yeah?
He's beneath you.
Anyone can see that.
You are all charm, ain't ya?
Now, how about you let me go?
I think you owe me a drink.
You really are a glutton
for punishment.
Do I look like I give a shit?
Vodka, straight up.
Single malt scotch on the rocks.
Thank you.
You better drink that quick.
'Cause when he sees you over
here, he'll be in your face
with a broken bottle,
before you can blink.
So listen to my eyes
and walk away.
Why don't you walk away,
I'll take my chances.
You got some bollocks on you,
I'll give you that.
When you're down there
gettin your face
stitched back on,
don't say I didn't warn you.
Look, we can dance around this
all night, or we can just
cut to the chance. I like you.
Well, you can't have me.
So put that in your pipe
and smoke it.
Get yourself a new watch
while you're at it.
That one's fucked.
You're very observant.
Oh, I have to be,
in my line, you know.
Fuck, here he comes.
What's going on here then?
Are you bothering my girl?
Here we go.
Never a dull fucking moment.
Will you excuse me, ladies?
He's nobody, he was just asking
for time, alright?
You hear that? You're nobody.
You wanna know what time it is.
It's time to fuck off, mate.
Go on.
There's a good boy.
Everything alright here, gents?
We're bailing. You've attracted
enough attention for one night.
Take care of it,
will you, Jimmy?
Oi, oi. Not so fast.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
That's Rob McNaughton.
The future love of my life.
Ex-marine, ex-con, excellent
in bed as it turned out.
And oh, yeah,
extremely fucking dangerous.
Billy Baraka
a mercenary from Angola.
Grew up fighting for freedom
in the civil war
before fighting for cash
in the Congo.
Teamed up with Rob
20 years ago.
And they've had each others
backs every fucking since.
Danny Oswald, ex-SAS.
Served his time in the sandbox,
before going into
the private sector and putting
his skills to better use.
Namely, profit.
He met Rob
in a South African jail.
Been thick as thieves
for ten years now.
These were
The Three Musketeers.
"All for one, one for all."
And anyone that fucked with
them, came a cropper.
Think it over.
Danny, I want to know
everything about her.
Certainly know
how to choose 'em, mate.
Choice has nothing
to do with it.
Hi, there.
Can I help you, darling?
I'm looking for someone.
Aren't we all?
Aunt Nellie,
smartest woman I know.
Mid-twenties, blonde hair,
blue eyes.
That'll be Scarlett.
She's over there
in the ring, love.
And you must be Aunt Nellie,
with the right hook?
Back in the day, love.
Back in the day.
It's a nice place you got here.
Some women buy hair salons
I bought this place.
It's got character.
I've got character.
This place has rats.
Scarlett, there's a young fellow
over here looking for you.
Jesus, young one.
How many times.
Keep your fucking guard up.
How the hell did you find me?
- I asked around.
- That's a bit stalkery.
No, stalking would be
unwanted attention.
Boyfriend, remember?
You're still flogging that shit?
We, uh, we haven't been
properly introduced.
I'm Robert. Friends call me Rob.
Scarlett.
Like Scarlett O'Hara?
My mum said I was born stubborn.
When are you going to learn
to stay down, girl?
Never.
- Where you from?
- The US originally.
But, uh, work keeps me overseas.
Oh, yeah,
what work is that then?
Supply and demand.
Based out of the Canaries,
but, uh
most of our product
comes from Africa.
- You've ever been there?
- Never been anywhere.
Oh, Africa is beautiful.
But she'll challenge you
every step of the way.
You like a challenge then?
If it ain't worth a fight
it ain't worth having.
You sound like gangster.
Do your worst.
I can go all day.
Keep 'em coming.
So what about you,
what's your game?
Never let them see me coming.
Not bad
for a skinny English girl.
So what about Friday night?
I told you, I can't.
What's the story with you two,
anyway?
I was going through some shit
and he helped me out.
- So you feel like you owe him.
- Yeah, something like that.
He's holding you back.
Look, I appreciate the effort,
mate.
But you're barking up
the wrong tree.
Will I see you again?
What do my eyes tell you?
Don't get me wrong,
I was fucking tempted.
But I ain't the kinda girl
who drops her knickers
'cause some bloke gives her
the time of day.
Time to pay a visit to the one
man I could always rely on.
You alright, lil' bro?
Hey, Dave,
have you got any crisps?
Uh, bottom cupboard.
And get me a beer,
I'm dryer than a nun's chuff.
Dave, my brother
from the same mother.
Loves a curry, cheats at cards.
Cheers.
I met a gangster today.
Oh, yeah. Al Capone was it?
I'm serious, you nob.
A proper fucking gangster.
He's desperate to get
in my knickers.
Oh, too much information.
Do you fancy him?
- I don't know.
- Of course you fucking do.
You want to be picking pockets
for that prick all your life?
No fucking way.
someone being, you know...nice
Makes me nervous.
You ain't afraid of nothing.
Just don't end up like mum
is all I'm saying.
Well...I think I missed
my chance now.
There's no point
stressing about it.
Alright, then, giz a go.
Alright, keep going up there.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
Nice one. That's gotta hurt.
Michelle, you ready?
- Babe, what's wrong?
- I feel like shit.
I think I'm coming down
with something.
Oh, fuck.
You should take the night off.
You're in no state to go out.
I can't, he'll go mental.
- You know what he's like.
- Well, fuck him.
You're his best earner, but you
ain't good to him like this.
Be an angel will you
and bring some chicken soup.
Of course, babe.
I'll see you later.
- Careful.
- Always.
Alright, I'm off out.
Well, stay out of bother.
And bring me back
something nice.
Yeah, whatever.
So there I was.
Back to the same old routine.
But I couldn't get him
out of my head.
Maybe if I hadn't been so
stubborn, so messed up.
Or maybe I won't get
a chance like that again.
It didn't matter.
If nothing else, it inspired me
to make a change
and take back control
of my life.
(Adam)
'What you think this is,'
'the fucking Ritz?'
'Get to fucking work,
or get back on the streets'
'where I found you.'
You lazy bitch.
What the fuck.
Fuck! Adam, stop. Stop!
Fuck!
Adam, you're going to
fucking kill her.
Adam! Argh!
Yeah.
Okay.
- Rob.
- Huh?
I don't know if you give a shit,
but...
But what?
You wanted to know everything
about the girl, right?
Scarlett Monaghan.
- There.
- Thank you.
Hey.
I didn't think
I'd see you again.
I did.
Doc, how's she doing?
Two cracked ribs,
multiple cuts and bruises
mainly to her own hands.
She put up a good fight.
But she won't say with who.
Maybe she'll tell you.
I already know.
Listen to me.
You're never going back there.
Where am I gonna go?
I can't go to Dave's,
if he sees me like this
he'll break Adam's fucking neck.
You care about that
piece of shit?
No, I don't want my brother
to go to jail.
Nobody's going to jail.
Now, you gotta trust me.
All my stuff's there and--
Forget it.
Forget about your stuff.
- We'll get you new stuff.
- What about Michelle?
He'll never lay another finger
on her or anyone else.
I guarantee it.
Yo, babe.
- Cooey.
- Who the fuck are youse?
♪ Hey hey hey ♪♪♪
Now...
We just have to figure out
what we're gonna do
about you, aren't we?
- Argh. Fuck.
- Shit. You okay?
Yeah, don't stop.
Don't worry.
I don't charge by the hour.
What? Oh, fuck, no.
My older brother Jack
gave it to me for my 18th.
Two weeks later
he was shot dead in the street.
I was standing next to him
when it happened.
The only reason I'm alive
is 'cause he pushed me clear.
That's how it got broken.
- You've worn it ever since?
- Yeah.
Reminds me of Jack
and what he did.
Old habits die hard.
We all have shit in our pasts.
Mum called it fertilizer.
Says it helps us grow.
Your mom sounds
like a smart lady.
The best.
Except when it come to men.
Your old man?
He was a drunk.
Just angry all the time.
He would come home from the pub.
Face like a beetroot,
stinking of beer and fags.
Then he'd beat
the shit out of her.
Me and my brother Dave
used to hide in my room.
We'd still hear the yelling
and screaming from downstairs.
Sometimes when I go to sleep
I can still hear it.
Piece of shit.
Where is he now?
He's rotting in jail
where he belongs.
A few years back,
he shot a security guard
on a botched robbery.
Got 20 years for that.
What a fuck up.
You're the first person
I've ever told that to.
I have to pee,
then you can fuck me again.
Days came and went,
bruises healed
and me and Rob
got closer and closer.
Anyone who's ever been in love,
will know exactly
what I'm talking about.
It's the best drug there is.
And I was high
as a fucking kite.
You know what I mean?
I'm sorry,
they're my best friends.
Move!
Robert.
Move back.
On me.
Stay behind me.
Stay behind me. Danny!
Move, mate. Move
Baraka!
Move, move. Shit!
Get in.
And that's when I saw him
for the first time.
The real Rob.
The man who'd die for me,
the man who'd kill for me.
Not a word of a lie.
It really turned me on.
- For fuck sake, Rob
- You guys okay?
- Yeah.
Danny, help me with this guy.
- We're gonna use their car.
- Alright.
Baraka, you take Scarlett
upstairs.
- Okay.
- No. no. I don't want to go.
Hey, hey, look,
you're gonna be fine
you go with Baraka
while I clean up this mess okay?
Look, you take this.
Look at me.
Hey, hey. I'm sorry.
I never meant to put you
in any danger.
If you're not here
when I get back...
I'll guard her with my life.
- Okay.
So do you reckon Charlie's boys?
No, this is too fucked up
even for Charlie.
So what's the plan?
The plan is,
we stick to the plan
and get the fuck out of town.
Baraka!
I sent him home.
You actually stayed.
You know I'm no
shrinking violet.
Like I know you
fly close to the wind.
That's part of the attraction
though, right?
Yeah.
Here, I kept it safe for you.
- You hurt yourself.
- It's alright.
No, let me take a look at that.
Deep breath.
Alright, hey, whoa, whoa.
Oh, my God.
You handled yourself
well tonight.
But the real test comes
when you run out of bullets.
I've been in a few fights.
No, I'm not talking about
the boxing ring.
I'm talking about a fight
till the death.
Where anything within reach
is a weapon,
you'll do whatever it takes
to stay alive.
That's when you find out
who you really are.
Here you go.
So why don't you tell me
who you really are.
Who those men were, who were
trying to kill us tonight.
Oh, not us, just me.
For this.
Is that what I think it is?
168 carats of it.
And I thought you peddled dope.
Did once, stole a few cars.
Did a little gun running.
Now I deal in diamonds.
The most important thing to know
about the diamond trade
is that it's dirty and corrupt.
Everybody's out to fuck you.
Now, all you can do
is have a code.
Me, I won't knowingly deal
in conflict diamonds.
But it's impossible to keep 'em
out of the mix.
You think your jeweler
on Bond Street or Fifth Avenue
really knows
where their rocks come from?
No. Truth is
they don't wanna know.
Now, 65% of the world's diamonds
comes from Africa.
This one here...
...was probably dug up
by some poor bastard
slogging his guts out
in a ditch somewhere.
Now, he finds it and he knows
it's worth a fortune.
What's he gonna do?
Fly to Antwerp?
No. So he takes
a big fucking risk
shoves it up his ass
and he smuggles it out
past the guards with machetes.
Then he sells it on
to someone local
for a few hundred bucks.
And then that guy marks it up
and sells it on
and so on and so on,
until it gets into the hands
of a local warlord,
now that's where I come in.
I deal with
the regional chiefs direct.
And they are very shrewd
when it comes to business.
You fuck with these guys
and they chop you into fish bait
and feed you to the crocodiles.
The rocks that I purchase
then go to Mumbai
where they get cut and graded.
And from there I sell
to my clients in the UK, China,
Russia and the biggest client
of all...
good ol' US of A.
Where those rocks ends up
adorning the fingers and necks
of movie stars, rap artists
and even a few royals.
- That's pretty fucking cool.
- Yeah.
It gets cooler.
I picked up this rock
for 500,000.
Within 24 hours
I got a call from Charlie.
Who's that?
Charlie is, uh...a legend
in the diamond trade.
She drinks with drug lords
and dines with ex-presidents.
- She?
- That's right.
She can place a stone
with any buyer in the world
from Saudi Princes
to Yakuza bosses.
And she wants this rock.
And she's made me an offer
that's well...
...it's hard to refuse.
How much?
15 mill.
And this is just a sample.
Charlie wants a regular supply.
- You can do that?
- Yeah.
This is the deal
that changes everything.
that gets us out.
So what happens now?
Well, now,
we do the trade with Charlie.
You wanna come?
- What can I do?
- Well, you could...
Watch my back.
Just make sure
you wear something, uh,
attention grabbing.
You want me to be a distraction?
No, no. I want you to look hot.
Mm, I'll give it a shot.
Hand-off's in 19 hours.
So until then we gotta sit
tight, keep this safe.
Well, I could think of a few
things to pass the time.
Scrabble and shit.
Not what I expected from
an international crime queen.
What is this place?
When she's not peddling
million dollar diamonds
Charlie runs a side hustle
in fine arts,
strictly for the wealthiest
of clientele.
Cushty.
Wow! Blimey!
This ain't too shabby.
More carats in here
than Sainsbury's.
And just, uh, be sure to keep
your fingers to yourself, okay?
Best behavior, cross my heart.
I'll let Victor know we're here.
Thanks.
Let's grab a drink.
- Robert.
- Hmm.
Welcome.
And you must be Scarlett.
Yeah. Word travels fast.
Scarlett, this is Victor.
Charlie's second cousin,
twice removed.
Ah, family business, yeah?
We keep our friends close
and our family closer.
Victor Resnick, ex-enforcer
for the Russian mob.
Now, he works for Charlie.
What about your enemies?
We have no enemies.
Please follow me.
Okay. Never forget.
Wait. Come.
Now, what do we have here?
Hmm. A big boy, yeah.
Easy boys. Any closer I'll have
to charge.
Hey, Charlie.
Charlie, looks like royalty,
swears like a docker.
Gentlemen, Scarlett.
Please, come on in.
Does everyone here know my name?
Scarlett Monaghan,
born in Peckham, 1995.
Nobody gets through these doors
that I don't know.
There were armed,
but, uh, nothing else.
Oh, my.
That's a big shiv, Baraka.
Planning on taking scalps?
Never know which way
the night is gonna go.
You are so right.
It seems we have some
trust issues to deal with.
So, ladies, skedaddle.
Go on.
If I am going into business
with someone
I like to know
who the fuck they are.
And the best way is to ask
who they fuck.
He doesn't need to wave a gun
in my face to get my attention
if that's what you mean.
Oh, I like this girl, Rob.
She's a keeper.
Do you trust him?
Yes, I do.
That's good.
Trust is very hard to find
these days.
And he respects me.
Sweet.
You see these ugly bastards?
There's not one of them
wouldn't take a bullet for me
some of them already have.
You know why?
'Cause these men are beasts.
Beasts respect one thing...
natural authority.
And you either have it,
or you don't.
Isn't that right, Rob?
That's been my experience,
yeah.
Why don't we all
calm the fuck down
and get on
with the business at hand?
It is time for the floor show.
Do you know this man, Scarlett?
- No, I don't.
- You certain?
You know a woman can always tell
if another woman is lying.
And if you are, I'll get
one of my boys to, uh,
drag you into the bathroom
and cut out your uterus
with a rusty knife.
- Still don't know him.
- Good.
Because this piece of shit...
...tried to steal
from my business partner.
Which is the same
as stealing from me.
And there's one thing
I can't abide is cuntery.
If you're squeamish,
look away now.
Victor!
Now, I learnt this...
...from a boyfriend...
...in...Bogotá.
- You alright?
- Didn't spill a drop.
'Hmm.'
You know...
...I could fetch
a couple of mill for that.
I can't say I'm not disappointed
you turning up empty handed.
Where the fuck
is my merchandise?
Scarlett, I think Charlie looks
like she could use a drink.
Well, fuck me sideways.
Oh!
You are beautiful.
Victor, pay the man.
Alright, take it.
I'll meet you out front.
Charlie, it is a pleasure
doing business with you.
One more thing before you go.
Now, that we're partners we're
more than friends, we're family.
Together we drink the blood
of our enemies.
Don't make a cunt out of me.
Here's to the first of many.
Budmo!
Fuck me, that was intense.
- What do you make of Charlie?
- She's off her fucking tits.
But I reckon
she's a straight shooter.
And you know this how?
Because I'm an excellent judge
of character.
Then why are you
with a crook like me?
'Cause you make me wetter
than an otter's pocket.
You know if I can't deliver,
it's my ass.
Pity, it's such a nice ass.
Nicely done. Duchess.
Why, did you just call her
Duchess?
Yeah. She handled that shit
with grace.
Like a Duchess.
Oh, why didn't you call her
a fucking, like
princess or something?
No. Duchess is better.
I like that.
Problem solved.
Stupid.
(Aunt Nellie)
'You should see him'
'before you go.'
'Fuck that.'
You can't be afraid of him
your whole fucking life.
Look, what used to I say to you
when you were close
to giving up a fight?
Forget the pain
and get back in the ring.
Right.
Because the pain goes away.
But the choices you make
stay with you forever.
You've never backed down
from a fight in your life.
'Well, look what'
'the cat dragged in.'
I see the girl I once knew
in the woman before me.
Well...
Nine years
and you have nothing to say?
Oh, cheers.
Don't thank me.
It speaks.
Those things will kill you.
Hmm.
You should be so lucky.
What the fuck
did mum ever see in you?
I had my moments.
Still do from time to time.
Jesus.
Do you feel anything
about what you did?
Doesn't pay
to dwell in the past in here.
No, down that road
they say lies madness.
What's done is done,
can't be undone.
I'm leaving.
Getting away from this place.
Away from you.
I just didn't want to go without
looking you in the eyes
one last time, to see if there's
a soul in there.
Well, what do you see?
Nothing worth saving.
You know you can choose
where you're going
but you can't change
where you came from.
You have my blood flowing
through your veins.
That means you're my girl
and you always will be.
- I ain't your fucking girl.
- Ah!
Yet here you are.
Looking for what?
Acceptance, absolution?
Closure, hmm?
You know, you can have
the lot of it, if you want
if it makes you feel better.
But don't come in here,
looking to save my soul.
Because I am beyond redemption.
I've been rotten to the core
since the day I was born.
Your mother knew that.
She stayed anyway.
No, she stayed out of fear
not love
Let me give you
some fatherly advice.
Stop looking for it to make
sense, because it never will.
Hmm?
If I could do it all again,
would I do things differently?
I'd still be the same old Frank.
Making the same old choices.
You know, I've long since come
to accept who I am.
Maybe it's time you did too.
Fucking hell.
To think I actually came here
to give you a chance.
Don't kid yourself.
You came here
to look in the mirror.
You just don't like
what you see.
You're wrong.
I ain't nothing like you.
I'm fucking ashamed
you're my father.
Uh-huh. But like it or not,
I am your father.
If you come near us,
ever again...
I will fucking kill you.
Ooh.
Hmm.
That's my girl.
Remember how I said,
this man would change my life?
Check this out.
I know what you're gonna say.
He's into some shady shit,
but I didn't care.
If I wasn't willing
to risk it all for love
then what's the point?
Welcome to your new home.
Fuck me.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Well...
...what do you think?
Fucking love it.
Come on. Come on.
Wow.
It was like coming home
for the first time.
And the whole gang was there
to welcome us.
Well. Santiago, Tom.
Santiago, this is Scarlett.
- Scarlett, Santiago.
- Hello, pretty.
There was Santiago,
Rob's local partner.
All chest hair
and too much cologne.
He started out smuggling drugs
for one of
the Galician cartels
in Spain.
Until Rob recruited him
alongside
his halfwit
younger brother Marco.
Well, the less said about him
the better.
- Johannes.
- Howzit.
The walking grease ball was
Johannes from South Africa
Santiago's hired gun
and definitely
a few sandwiches
short of a picnic.
And last but not least.
And my oldest
and dearest friend.
Tom Sullivan.
Tom, this is Scarlett.
Rob may have mentioned you
a few hundred times.
Sounds like I got a bit of
catching up to do.
I know all of his deepest,
darkest secrets.
Enough tequila, you might
just get it out of me.
Fuck you, Tom.
Scarlett, welcome.
To Casa Bling.
Santiago, what's, uh, what's
with the welcome committee?
It's not really your style,
is it?
We heard about
what happened in London.
We are a little concerned.
Huh? I got to talk to the guys.
Why don't you settle in?
Maria will take care of
anything you need, okay?
- Hola, señora.
- See you in a bit?
- Yeah.
- Would you like a drink?
Me and you
are gonna be best mates.
Let's talk.
Look, whatever shit went down,
we delivered the merch
and Charlie's happy.
Let's just make sure it stays
that way.
Do you think it was
a rival crew?
They knew the exact time
and place.
Had to be an inside job.
Rob, you're still with us?
- This is fucking serious.
- Yeah, no shit, Santiago.
What's the word on the street?
We talked to
all of our usual sources.
Nobody knows shit.
Or they are too afraid to talk.
Then we make 'em talk.
Whoever is fucking with us
is already dead.
They just don't know it yet.
In England
there's a class system.
Where you're born,
which school you go to
how to pronounce
your fucking Ts.
It's been like that
for a thousand fucking years.
And it ain't about to change.
But down here
no one gives a monkey's.
The only rule
is survival of the fittest.
And that's a rule
I can relate to.
♪ Hey hey hey hey ♪♪
There she is.
Good morning, beautiful.
- You like my pet?
- Cute.
Can you make her sit?
Well, let's do this.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
You okay? Oh!
I just want to say
I fucking love you.
You're incredible.
You know that?
- I have my moments.
- I'll see you later, okay?
See you later.
[engine turnover]
- Good morning, boss.
- Not a fucking word.
- Good morning, Maria.
- Good morning, señora.
You wants something?
English tea?
Hmm, I know
my way around the kitchen.
Señora, it's no trouble.
Alright, but only if you give it
a rest with the señora
and join me for a cuppa.
Okay.
Nice work.
Good job.
How's my favorite greengrocer
Kamal?
- What the fuck?
- What?
- Down!
Rob!
We can't stay here.
Get the fuck out of here.
Let's move.
Move.
Changing.
Nice shot.
Unit.
Move.
They got us boxed in.
Who the fuck are these guys?
How do we get out of this one,
Butch?
This is how.
Come here. Get behind me.
Come here.
[explosion]
Go get the truck!
Let's go! Let's go!
Hey, there.
No!
Why don't you
just give me what I want?
Hey!
Do you like to play rough?
- You little English bitch.
- Get the fuck out of my house.
Sorry. Can't do that.
Maria, get behind me.
What? You think
I came here for her?
What can I tell you?
It was him or me.
But looking at him laying there
bleeding on the floor
I didn't feel a fucking thing.
Maybe I was more like
me old man than I thought.
But I also knew
I rocked the boat big time.
And I didn't know
how Rob would take it.
Oh, fuck.
Shit, shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit.
You alright?
Yeah, yeah, Rob.
Little bit of an issue.
You okay?
Thank you, Duchess.
Come here.
Where's Scarlett?
- She's upstairs, mate.
- Shit!
Get rid of that.
Baraka, give him a hand.
I'll go get a rope.
Maria, hey.
It's not safe for you here.
Okay?
You take this.
You never come back.
You understand?
- You understand?
- Gracias, Senor Robert.
No, no. Oh.
For fuck sake.
(Rob)'Scarlett!'
Scarlett!
Are you hurt?
I'm alright.
Fuck.
Talk to me.
What the fuck!
Rob, talk to me.
Please.
I could've lost you.
One, two, three.
Come and get it.
Oh.
- Yeah.
- Marco's dead.
- What the fuck happened?
- Look, it doesn't matter.
He was a fucking pig
and he got what he deserved.
'Alright, Rob,
I need you to listen to me.'
He came to my fucking house,
he came after Scarlett.
He crossed a line.
This was Jack's problem,
he never listened.
Alright, I'm listening.
Marco was a piece of shit,
but blood is blood, Rob
and Santiago isn't just gonna
let this go.
Well, at least we know who's
trying to fuck us now, right?
For now, I just need you
and Scarlett
to get to a safe house
and lay low.
'What about you?'
Santiago is a business man
I'm gonna try to appeal
to his sense of greed.
If not?
Then you my friend
are gonna do what you do best
kill the son of a bitch.
- You got everything?
- I think so.
Let's go grab that one.
- Rob, meet us out front.
- Yeah.
Okay. Come on, guys,
let's go.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
- Thanks, Danny.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
- Come on, come on.
Going somewhere?
Santiago.
You piece of shit.
Why don't you just
make yourself at home, huh?
There is an old saying, Rob.
That seems pertinent
to this occasion.
Never invite
a vampire into your house
it renders you powerless.
Well, this is all about blood
do you mind if
I just have one last drink?
- Be my guest.
- You wanna join me?
Fuck you.
We always said,
business comes first.
No matter what.
But this just got very personal.
You know...
I always knew that someday,
someone would step up
to challenge me.
I just hoped
that when that day came
they'd have the balls
to look me in the eye
and not stab me in the back.
He was my brother, Rob.
You of all people
should understand that.
But... I'm a reasonable man.
Business first, right?
So you want
the Charlie deal to go through?
And I want my pound of flesh.
Hey, hey.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you, okay?
You can't threaten me anymore,
Rob.
There was a time when nobody
would fuck with you.
You had the world by the balls.
[blows]
And you let it go.
Is that what this is about?
You want the old Rob back?
You know, you should be
careful what you wish for.
The old Rob may have been crazy,
but at least
I could respect him.
This new Rob,
all talking and no...
Run!
No!
You really should put that girl
on a chain.
She's out of control.
What did I say, Rob?
You never fucking listen.
Now, it's too late.
No. No, you fucker.
- Rob.
- Fuck, that was uncalled for.
How long have we know
each other?
How long has it taken us
to build this?
20 fucking years.
But where has your old pal Tom
been all that time?
Right by your side.
Always the bridesmaid,
never the fucking bride, huh?
Fuck you.
I've sacrificed way too much
to stand by and watch you
piss it all away
for a fucking skirt.
I will not let that happen.
For the record.
It was Santiago
who told Marco to kill Scarlett.
I thought it was a bad move.
Seems I was right.
As for you...
...that's on me.
You piece of shit. You're dead.
No, Rob, you are.
Just like your no good brother.
I'm gonna fucking
tear your heart out.
- Get 'em out of here.
- No.
Baraka, the loyal dog.
Faithful to the end.
Better a dog, than a rat.
You know power
commands treachery.
Otherwise it stagnates.
You know, sooner or later
someone's gonna try
to take it away from me.
I just hope, I don't get screwed
over for something as stupid
as love.
See, Rob loves his bitch,
you love your friend.
Look where it's gotten you.
Now, I've heard
you like to feed the animals.
So why don't you go
feed the animals.
Your choice, bro. Dead or alive?
You talk too much,
get it over with.
Why waste a good bullet
on a piece of shit like you.
Alright, drop it.
Who's the piece of shit now?
They've taken Rob and Scarlett.
What the fuck we gonna do, B.?
What the fuck can we do?
It's just us now.
[trembles]
(Rob)'Hey.'
Hey, come here.
You know, I've been thinking
when we get through this shit...
what do you say
we get married?
Santiago was wrong.
There is some crazy still
left in you, isn't there?
Because I wanna marry you?
'Cause you think we're gonna
get through this shit.
Whatever happens, I got you.
Oh, shit.
Lee-Roy and Nacho...
Tom's muscle
and a right pair of cunts.
You got any famous last words?
Fuck you.
I expected something better.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Don't be afraid.
- Tom wanted to be sure.
- No, no, no.
- You got this in the front.
- You're gonna be okay.
No!
No, no!
No! No, no.
No!
You fuckers. You fuckers.
Say goodbye, bitch.
They look kinda sweet.
Laying there like that.
Fuck this.
Leave the dogs... to do
the clean-up.
- Let's get a beer, bro.
- Let's go.
[inhales]
[plane droning]
[wailing]
I never felt so empty
in all my life.
I couldn't feel pain.
I couldn't feel anything.
My one true love was gone,
just like that.
All I could do
was take what I could carry
and get the fuck out.
(Aunt Nellie)
What used to I say to you
when you were close
to giving up a fight.
You've never backed down
from a fight in your life.
This is Scarlett.
Can we meet?
Scarlett,
it's good to see you again.
Though I wish it were under
different circumstances.
Rob was a good man.
The best.
That's why I came here
to make sure
his legacy
doesn't die with him.
I only agreed to this meeting
out of respect for Rob.
Well, I admire your spirit,
but, uh
let's get fucking serious.
You're nobody
with nothing to bargain with.
You're no skin off my back,
if you were to
fuck off and die in a ditch.
But I like you so, uh
I won't help you to do that.
Victor...show Ms. Scarlett
the door.
Oi.
Do you really think
I'm the kinda girl
who's gonna let this go, hmm?
Hmm? Alright.
I will give you four
and a half minutes.
I'm gonna take it back.
The entire operation.
And if I succeed I'll deliver
everything Rob promised you.
If you succeed.
Do you know what it takes to
survive as a woman in our world?
It's not enough to be
as good as a man
you have to be twice as smart.
Twice as ruthless,
three times a lady
and ten times a bitch.
No ifs, buts or maybes.
You better fucking succeed,
or they will eat you alive.
And, um...
...from where I'm sitting
I don't think
you've got what it takes.
So, I am sorry for your loss.
But from now on I'll be dealing
with the other side.
Hmm.
Don't suppose I can convince
you otherwise.
I listened, that's as good as
you're gonna get from me.
Okay.
- Whoa.
- How about now?
Pick pocket, bitch.
Anybody move, I'll blow
her fucking brains out.
I told you I liked you
but you really are trying
my patience.
Desperate fucking times,
desperate fucking measures.
Do you know how many people have
drawn a gun on me and lived?
Not too many, I should think.
Zero. Point zero.
They killed every part of me.
Left me with nothing
but skin and bone.
Then you should be very grateful
they left you that
and get out while you can.
If you had the choice again,
would you?
Mm.
Then you know
I have to see this through.
Two weeks.
Either it's done,
or I'm dead in a ditch.
Or kill me now
and be done with it.
That's how you're going
to beat 'em.
When I was little,
my grandmother used to
tell me stories about a woman
from her hometown
they called Lady Death.
This was in the Ukraine.
Her real name was
Lyudmila Pavlichenko.
She would have been about your
age when she joined the army
to fight the Nazis attacking
Sevastopol in 1941
and her particular skill was
with a rifle, a long-range, and
she was so fucking
good at it.
She eventually chalked up
309 confirmed deaths.
That's more than any of the men
did in her unit.
I mean, she became
a national hero.
And she was as tireless
and fearless
and ruthless a bitch, as you
could ever care to meet.
And I think, that you two
would have got along.
Come on. Skedaddle.
Go kill 'em all
and when you're done, call me.
As long as you're still alive,
the deal stands.
- Hey. Stop, stop, stop.
- Hey.
- It's me.
- Let go, Danny.
So you can slot him
in the street.
It's a big fucking plan, is it?
- I just want him dead.
- Yeah, well.
You know, well, so do I.
But you can't get emotional
about this kinda shit.
You gotta remain detached.
This is what I do, so let me
fucking help you.
What about Baraka?
- Did he make it?
- We split up. It's safer.
Well, if he's smart I think
he'll be long gone.
- That means it's just us then.
- Yeah.
You in?
Yeah.
Are you gonna come in?
Or you gonna stand there
and drool.
You got a mouth on you.
What else is it good for?
Fuck sake.
♪ Lost your love of life? ♪
♪ Too much apple pie ♪
♪ Oh have you
lost your love of life? ♪
♪ Too much apple... ♪♪♪
Have some fucking dignity.
You won't kill me.
You don't have the balls, bitch.
What have balls got
to do with it?
Jesus!
[indistinct]
Oh, fucking hell.
Get in the fucking car, Duchess.
Where the fuck
did you come from?
I've been staking out this place
for a week.
Imagine my surprise seeing a
dead woman walk out the door.
Good to see you too.
Danny, keeping out of trouble,
I see.
Then explain to me what
the hell you were thinking?
Who knew he'd fall out
the fucking window
things didn't go to plan?
Things rarely do.
Instead of bitching about it,
why don't you help us out?
What is she talking about?
I'm talking about
taking back the kingdom, Baraka.
I'm gonna kill every last
fucker that betrayed Rob
and I'm just getting started.
You put her up to this,
didn't you?
Are you fucking
out of your mind?
I've never been so clear
about anything in all my life.
What happened to you?
I've nothing else left to lose.
How about your life?
They can't kill me,
I'm already dead.
Do you have any idea
what you're up against?
I don't care.
Oh, come on, B.
Won't be a party without you,
mate.
You're as crazy as she is.
If I help...
it's just this once,
then I am done.
Once is all we need.
Just so you understand, Duchess,
what're you're asking
is a blood oath.
We do this,
or we die trying.
With Danny out of action,
we'll need an extra hand.
That's very fucking funny, mate.
Do you know anyone we can trust?
Family.
But first we need to get you
off the street.
I know a place.
We couldn't go
via the hospital, could we?
[clears throat]
Sorry we're...
Dios mio!
Duchess, you're alive?
It's a nice place you got here.
It's cozy.
It needs some work, but...
But what are you doing here?
I need your help.
I can't offer much besides, a
cold beer and a place to hide.
But I will never forget
what you did for me, Duchess.
My place is yours.
(Johannes)
'Whoever it was, they'
fucked Nacho up real good.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Fucking Rob's pitbull Baraka
avenging his master's death.
Do you think we should
warn the others?
Not yet.
Maybe there is a play
to be made here.
Like Victor said, it pays
to keep your family close.
This is Jono, Baraka's nephew
and our first recruit.
- To our friend.
- To Rob.
Uncle!
Jono.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
- Danny.
- Alright.
- Nice to meet you.
- So...
What are we doing
in this shit hole?
This is my place, asshole.
If you don't like it,
you can stick it up your ass.
That is Maria
and she is with us.
Sorry.
So you deal dope,
we deal diamonds.
That's Fredo,
a right slippery customer.
Rob never fucked
with your business...
...and you never
fucked with his.
Everything was, uh...cushty.
So why are you now sticking your
beak in where it doesn't belong?
Shit, girl, I dunno
what you're talking about.
Word is you are sheltering
one of Rob's killers.
I wanna know where.
Listen, Duchess,
or whatever your name is.
You want to play
in a man's world
you better be ready to get
fucked in the ass.
We all get fucked in the ass
sooner or later.
That's the world we live in.
Man or woman, we all
look the same from behind.
Why don't you just tell me
where he is.
Be a lot easier that way.
I already told you,
I don't know shit.
Call it female intuition, but...
I think you're telling me
porky pies.
Now, what is a pork and--
Tell me where he is,
you fucking slag
or I'll skewer something else
to the table.
- Where is he?
- Alright. Alright.
I don't know where he is,
but I know someone who does.
His name is Riff. Riff.
Cushty.
(Jono)
'So what's she like?'
What, Baraka hasn't told you?
No.
- You hadn't told him.
- Nope.
Well, mate, she's like...
...she's like a fucking banshee.
Really?
Yeah, she wears this like,
massive tribal necklace
that she made
with all the balls
of the men that she's killed.
Yep.
That's our Duchess.
So you better be careful with
that loud mouth of yours or...
...snip snip.
She say you can go in now.
[speaks in foreign language]
You're getting blood
on the floor.
Hey...
Here. Duchess never forgets
a friend.
[door closes]
- Oi.
- Yeah.
- You coming or what?
Chop, chop.
You must be Jono.
Duchess.
Come in, come in,
park your ass.
Did Baraka tell you
what you're getting into?
- He did.
- And you still came anyway.
I ain't afraid of trouble.
Not if it's for family.
But I ain't your family.
Uncle said you're like
a daughter to him.
That makes us cousins.
- I have only one question.
- What's that?
How the fuck we gonna take down
the entire organizations
with two guys, two girls
and one armed bandit?
- Careful.
- No offense.
Good question.
Look, if we go head to head
with these fuckers
we'll get creamed.
So we have to outsmart them.
Hit them, one by one.
and maybe if I live long enough
I'll get to use Tom's balls
as earrings.
I thought it was a necklace.
For you I'll make it into
fucking cufflinks.
How about that?
Alright.
Yeah, but what we're really
gonna need is more men.
And big fucking guns.
Men and guns don't come cheap.
At least not the ones
worth having.
Holy fucking shit.
When the time comes we'll have
all the men and guns we need.
But a move like that,
draws too much attention.
As long as they think I'm dead,
we have an advantage.
Let's use it.
What did you have in mind?
When I was learning how to
pick pockets, I would study
how street magicians
would draw your attention
away from
what's really going on.
They're too busy
looking at your tits
they ain't seen your hand
lift their wallet.
We apply a little misdirection
the fuckers won't see us coming.
Ain't that right, Michelle?
Easy boys, she's with me.
- Glad you could make it.
- Glad you asked.
Everyone this is my mate,
Michelle.
Hi, Michelle.
- Welcome to the nuthouse.
- The nuthouse?
Yeah. You have to be crazy
to be here.
Alright.
Baraka, we need to make
a house call.
Who's the target?
Riff, low level gun for hire.
Been known to do
the odd job for Tom.
Fuck.
What the hell you were thinking,
man?
I dunno, it's a reflex
action, is that.
Ninja and shit.
- Okay.
- Ow.
Oh, fuck. Fuck you.
I already told you, I dunno
where the fuck he's at.
Fuck you. Get me out.
But the trouble is, Riff,
you're a lying piece of shit.
Oh, stop. Fuck.
I'm nothin', okay.
They don't give me the time
of the fucking day
I can't tell you
what I don't know, right?
Is that how you wanna play?
Okay.
He's all yours, Duchess.
'What the fuck.'
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where you going? Wait, wait.
Stop, stop, stop it.
Wait, wait.
Well?
Well, what?
Fuck.
No more piss-assing about, Riff.
(Baraka)
'I'm worried about her.'
Since she came back,
she's changed.
Something definitely got
fucking broken out there.
Can't be fixed.
The quicker you speak,
the quicker the pain stops.
Hey. Wait, wait, wait.
What're you doing?
Wait, wait, wait.
Please, please, please.
Where is Lee-Roy?
I don't know.
He's hiding in his chop shop.
He's hiding in his chop shop
by the airport. Stop.
[crying]
(Baraka)
'That's enough, Duchess.'
[coughs]
Hey.
I ever see you again...I come
back to finish the job.
Cool off.
Fuck.
Any chance we could, uh...
...pop by the hospital?
[plane droning]
(Jono)
'Two out front, well armed.'
'No sign of Lee-Roy.'
Copy that.
He's in there.
If you ask me, Duchess,
and you haven't,
this is a trap
and Lee-Roy is the bait.
Don't care. I'm going in anyway.
And I go where she goes, mate.
Quit encouraging her.
You want to live forever?
Nope.
You know, I wouldn't mind.
Okay, Jono, you're up.
- Stay the fuck back.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy guys.
Take it easy, take it easy.
I come in peace as you can see.
I brought you some
tasty chicken calientes.
Take a good look.
Gorgeous, right?
Fuck.
- Can't open the gate.
- Fuck it.
Let's get this party started.
Click fucking clack.
Get to the back-up car
and keep the engine running.
I got this.
[dramatic music]
Up top.
Go.
It's Lee-Roy.
I'm going after him.
Duchess, watch out.
- Shit. Shit, shit, shit.
- Shit.
You've got company.
Get out of there.
[dramatic music]
Give it up, B. It's all over.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
It was good knowing you, mate.
[dramatic music]
[machine whirring]
I was just following orders.
And now you're gonna die for it.
Please, Scarlett.
Scarlett's dead,
my name's Duchess.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
- Yeah.
- 'Welcome back from the grave.'
I never talked
to a corpse before.
- Me neither.
- We have your friends.
But I'm prepared
to offer you a deal.
Their lives for yours.
Alright. I'm in.
You still with us, Scarlett?
That's right. Stare daggers.
I know how much
you'd like to kill me right now.
And if I were in your shoes
I'd feel the same way.
What the fuck is so funny?
I'm just trying to picture you
wear my shoes.
It looks bad I know.
Baraka was right, things rarely
do turn out the way you plan,
but stay with me on this.
Don't make me do that again.
Go and piss up a rope.
You know, you've been
pretty busy
since your little resurrection.
But after you killed Nacho,
it didn't take a fucking genius
to figure out
you'd come after Lee-Roy next.
Still two for two.
- I'm impressed.
- Aw.
You're easily impressed,
ain't you?
- Fuck you.
- No, fuck you.
You know what, Scarlett?
I just, I just gotta make sure
that Rob doesn't come through
that fucking door.
Didn't you hear?
He's dead.
Like you?
Bring them out here.
Wait, I thought we had a deal.
You gave me your word.
You think I'm a man of my word?
No. Danny.
I'm alright.
Oh, you fucker.
Go on and take your fucking
septic cuts.
He's dead, alright.
Well, unfortunately
your being here,
is proof to the contrary.
Sorry, Danny boy.
Fuck you!
- Fucking dead!
- Alright.
Fuck.
Ahh!
You know it's no fun,
when they don't scream anymore.
I guess we're gonna have
to try something else.
I'm gonna enjoy
the hell out of this.
[drill machine whizzing]
Fuck you.
And when I'm done
lobotomizing Baraka...
the girls are next.
Jesus Christ! He's dead,
he's fucking dead, alright!
You know what?
I believe you.
I think...I'm gonna be able to
sleep a little easier tonight.
You know...
I know why
you really killed Rob.
And it wasn't just about
the business.
Oh, yeah?
Enlighten me.
Rob had everything.
Not just the power...
...the looks, the charm...
...the style. What have you got?
[cracks neck]
You got some balls on you,
princess.
No, I don't, that's the point.
And it's Duchess, dickhead.
Hey, Johannes.
What if I give you
a million dollars
to shoot him in the head
right now?
Oh, is, is that your big plan?
To turn us against each other?
No, you already did that.
You killed Rob and his brother.
Johannes, you think
a man like this
is willing to share the power?
Won't be long before it's your
neck on the chopping block.
- Don't even think about it.
- Think about what?
Is she right, bru? You're
planning on killing me too?
Don't you see
she's fucking with you?
- Am I?
- Maybe I kill you first, huh?
Boys, boys, boys.
Don't you think
if my plan to go after Lee-Roy
was pretty fucking obvious
to you two
maybe it was pretty
fucking obvious to me too?
What?
[dramatic music]
Rob once told me...
...that power, real power...
...can never be given,
it has to be taken.
Look around, that's what
I'm doing, you stupid bitch.
No, no. That's what you think
you're doing.
Fuck you,
I don't have time for this.
[explosion]
Men with big fucking guns,
remember?
Turns out, diamonds are
a girls best friend.
No. No.
[drill machine whizzing]
[dramatic music]
Duchess.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Drop it, sunshine.
- Stay back.
- Show me your hands.
He's mine.
You wanna show me
how big your balls really are?
Come to daddy.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
This is where your story ends...
Princess.
Do your worst.
Scarlett, please.
It wasn't personal.
Don't. You butchered Rob.
Doesn't get more personal.
But if it makes you feel better.
It was a pleasure doing
business.
Oh, fuck.
I think we did enough for today.
Fuck, yeah.
You took your precious
fucking time.
I was running out of bullshit.
I find that fucking hard
to believe.
Oi, watch it, dipstick.
Oh, that's gratitude for you.
Come on, boys.
Get your shit together.
How you doing, Duchess?
We did it. We fucking did it.
No. You did it.
I made it through,
by the skin of my teeth.
And there I was with my own
fucked up little family.
It should have been perfect
but there would always
be one thing missing.
You alright, guys?
Here, fill your boots.
You're not shitting me,
are you?
You've earned it.
- How's your arm, Danny?
- Tickety-boo.
Duchess... it's Charlie.
Charlie.
'Somehow, I knew
you'd pull it off.'
Your first shipment
arrives on Friday.
I expect payment on delivery.
What kind of a cunt
do you think I am?
'Paying kind, of course.'
I think you and I could do great
things together.
Maybe...
In another life, but, uh...
I've come to the end of the line
right now.
Baraka will be taking over
from now on.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Ciao, Charlie.
Did that bitch
just hang up on me?
Duchess...
I did what I set out to do,
Baraka.
And now I'm done.
Look after them for me.
So here I am, I've come
a long way in a short time.
At the end of the day,
I am what I am.
I talk dirty, I hit hard,
I drink my vodka straight.
And I don't take shit
from anyone.
I've loved, I've lost.
I've taken power
and I've earned my respect.
Revenge may be a dish
best served cold
but it taste bitter sweet.
I did what I had to do
and now I choose to walk away.
Because that's what Rob
would have wanted.
Riff.
[explosion]
Hold your horses,
did I say you could leave yet?
[rewind]
Now, let's try again, shall we?
[explosion]
My name is Duchess
and I live by one simple rule.
Never let 'em see me coming.
Oi!
♪ I've been feeling
like I'm drowning ♪
♪ In an ocean full of memories ♪
♪ I might be losing my mind ♪
♪ Over bruises on fields ♪
♪ Will I ever feel the silence ♪
♪ Like something new
than an enemy ♪
♪ Will I ever love again ♪
♪ The way that I did ♪
♪ I close my eyes and dream ♪
♪ Of brighter days
brighter days ♪
♪ Close my eyes
and dream of you ♪
♪ Diamonds in my heart ♪
♪ Shining bright
when your arms around me ♪
♪ I would die a 1000 times
for you to find me ♪
♪ Diamonds in my heart ♪
♪ Shining bright
when your arms around me ♪
♪ I would die a 1000 times
for you to find me ♪
♪ I will burn all the bridges ♪
♪ That life built against
our love ♪
♪ What I feel is timeless ♪
♪ I'm forever yours ♪
♪ I would lie if I said I'm not
reckless broken or lost ♪
♪ But I've been
in darker places before ♪
♪ I close my eyes and dream
of brighter days brighter days ♪
♪ Close my eyes
and dream of you ♪
♪ Diamonds in my heart ♪
♪ Shining bright
when your arms around me ♪
♪ I would die a 1000 times
for you to find me ♪
♪ I found home in your eyes ♪
♪ The kinda peace
is hard to find ♪
♪ A safe place
where I can hide ♪
♪ I refuse to say goodbye ♪
♪ I found home in your eyes ♪
♪ The kind of peace
is hard to find ♪
♪ A safe place
where I can hide ♪
♪ I refuse to say goodbye ♪
♪ Diamonds in my heart ♪
♪ Shining bright
when your arms around me ♪
♪ I would die a 1000 times
for you to find me ♪♪♪