♪ Now can you clap
for the killers? ♪
♪ Give it up
for them gangsters ♪
♪ One time for the killers ♪
♪ Double up
for them gangsters ♪
♪ Well, I wrote this
for criminals ♪
♪ But all of y'all
should listen at me ♪
♪ Now if you ever
catch me snitchin' ♪
♪ Just haul off and slap me ♪
♪ They on the other team ♪
♪ Let's rumble
Is my thoughts exactly ♪
♪ They work for gangsters ♪
♪ And they wacked
Fred Hampton Jr.'s Pappy ♪
♪ Ay, playboy
Pop 'em with a pistol ♪
♪ And get executed ♪
♪ Ay, mama
Murder 'em with missiles ♪
♪ And you get saluted ♪
♪ Go head and gank 'em
for a grand ♪
♪ It's DNA computed ♪
♪ But bankers bathe
in the Bahamas ♪
♪ Off of billions looted ♪
♪ Now can you clap? ♪
♪ Now can you clap
for them killers? ♪
♪ Give it up
for them gangsters ♪
♪ One time for the killers ♪
♪ Double up
for them gangsters ♪
♪ But they the ones
who wrote the laws ♪
♪ Not for
them Coppola criminals ♪
♪ They just act hard ♪
♪ Tony Montana had a stylist
and a SAG card ♪
♪ When he reloaded ♪
♪ Slaves forgot
that they had back scars ♪
♪ Ay, Mister DeNiro
What kind of gun is that? ♪
♪ Can you look more
like a menace? ♪
♪ Take two
Now run it back ♪
♪ Ay, so what Scorsese
Got all them money stacks ♪
♪ Long as his lens
never looks ♪
♪ At the real maniacs ♪
♪ Clap for them killers ♪
♪ Give it up
for them gangsters ♪
♪ One time for the killers ♪
♪ Double up
for them gangsters ♪
Joseph, I meant to remind you,
no blood! The opera house
is 139 years old.
Well, at least
the carpet's red.
What difference
would 10 seconds make?
It can't.
Drop your weapon!
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
I got you. Come on.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Do you know what happened?
A dangerous world, I guess.
- Is your foot okay?
- Yeah.
Hey.
What's your name?
Uh...
Joe.
Thank you, Joe.
Are you okay?
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, do you have water, please?
Please, come.
Shit.
Okay, there's nothing here
to indicate any tumors
- so we can rule that out.
- All right.
That is one hell of a resume
you've got there.
Yeah, there's no substitute
for experience.
Yeah.
Is that really necessary?
What, all this
and you're scared of a needle?
You don't know what I can do
with that needle.
Man up, soldier.
You know,
in all the years, Joe,
how many hits to the head
do you think you've taken?
Define hit.
You know, saw stars,
blacked out,
threw up, that kind of thing.
Uh, I never threw up.
Yeah, I guess I've had
my bell rung
- a few times.
- Mm.
It's just,
repeated head trauma
can lead to CTE
which the scans can't detect.
What are you saying?
I'm saying it might be time
to reevaluate your lifestyle,
Sergeant Flood.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
I'll run some more tests.
Joseph,
it's 11 o'clock already.
You know I worry
when you're late.
You worry because
worrying is what you do.
I had to see Doc Kagen.
He says hi.
You were wounded?
No, I've been
having these really
bad headaches. I told you.
Doctors.
- What do doctors know?
- Yeah.
Well, I've been having
double vision as well, so...
That's bad.
In this game, you wouldn't
know what target to shoot.
Are you gonna
drink that coffee
or just stir it to death?
Don't you worry
about my coffee.
So, I spoke to our friend.
The police are working
on a theory
that one of Petrov's
own security team
did the hit. You're clean.
Am I?
Are you asking professionally
or philosophically?
I don't know.
Sometimes I ask myself,
"Why the hell do I do this?"
Petrov was scum,
trafficking women.
You did the world a favor.
What will they say about me
when someone takes me
off the board?
Will anyone even notice?
Leave judgement to God.
Our job is simply
to arrange the meeting.
Now for the good news.
What good news?
The $750,000 you just made,
30% to the laundry...
...minus expenses...
Gonna buy you
a new calculator.
Minus my commission.
Cheap at half the price.
We're gonna need to talk
about some of these expenses.
You need a vacation.
Get some sun.
Meet a nice girl.
Where am I
gonna meet a nice girl?
Who knows
where you'll meet her?
Just get me another gig.
Joseph, never get
so busy making a living
that you forget
to make a life.
Did you read that
on a fortune cookie?
That's Dolly Parton,
my friend.
♪ Give me a word
Give me a sign ♪
♪ Show me where to look ♪
♪ And tell me
what will I find? ♪
♪ What will I find? ♪
♪ Lay me on the ground
And fly me in the sky ♪
♪ Show me where to look ♪
♪ And tell me
What will I find? ♪
Rehearsals are closed
to the public.
Uh, belongs
to one of your dancers.
Thanks.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Joe?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I had that.
You've had this
this whole time?
Yeah.
Wow, you really
are a lifesaver.
First time I've heard that.
Well, you saved mine.
How's your foot?
It's good. It's nothing.
Just a little bruised.
Can I buy you dinner?
You know, just as a...
as a thank you.
Um...
Unless you can't because...
because you can't.
No, it's not that.
It's just...
Okay. I'll just
give you my number.
I have to get back
to rehearsal,
but I'll be done at five.
So call me...
if you...
want to.
"Maze."
Maize.
What?
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Heaven
Let your light shine ♪
Maize.
Good to see you today.
Good to see you today?
All that dancing
must make you hungry.
No.
'Sup, girl?
It's Joe.
I'd love to.
Send.
Mmm.
Where do you put it all?
Before we started the show,
we were rehearsing
eight hours a day.
Now we're at four hours a day,
six shows a week.
I cannot do that
on celery and rice cakes.
How'd you end up in Budapest?
Milos, she's one of the best
choreographers in the world.
Yeah.
The show was incredible
up until...
- The murder and shooting?
- Yeah.
That wasn't
in the program notes.
How did you end up here?
I don't run into
many Americans.
Work.
I travel all over Europe
and this was central,
affordable, low-key.
You got family?
Uh...
I joined the army
when I was 18.
I'm not sure
anybody noticed when I left.
I didn't think to remind them.
What do you do now?
Retirement planning.
What?
Could you help a dancer
who needs to retire soon?
You're too young to retire.
Dancers are like boxers.
Father Time
remains undefeated.
Don't you love dancing?
The last 10 years,
two ankle surgeries
torn ligaments,
stress fractures.
I'm not complaining.
I love dance. I really do.
My mom had to work two jobs
to afford my ballet classes
so to me, it could
never be just a hobby.
So I was thinking
when I retire
I could start a dance school
for kids like me.
A place where
they get to decide
who they really want to be.
It all sounds
a bit too crazy, but...
I don't think so.
No. I think it sounds perfect.
Well, if that doesn't work out,
I can always become
a cat burglar.
I'll need
a good getaway driver.
Mm. That seems risky.
Any benefits?
Me in a cat suit, duh!
Where do I send
my application?
Did you just laugh?
- No.
- You did.
- I definitely did not.
You're smiling right now.
- Am I?
- It suits you.
- Maybe.
- It really does.
(I GOT YOU BY LOLO FT.
♪ Huh! Huh! ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ I really like
the way you move ♪
♪ You're like
a pocket full of jewels ♪
♪ The headline in my news ♪
♪ I wanna tell you
I do, I do, I do ♪
♪ I like the dirt
in your hair ♪
♪ I got you
I do ♪
♪ I got a one-track mind
and it's you this time ♪
♪ I got you
I do ♪
♪ I got a one-track mind ♪
- ♪ All right ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
- Oh, you're not ticklish.
- I'm not.
- It makes no sense.
- I'm not ticklish.
♪ I like the way
you hold your money ♪
♪ Ooh
I really want you, I do ♪
♪ I do, I do ♪
♪ I got you ♪
- ♪ I do ♪
♪ I got a one-track mind
and it's you this time ♪
- ♪ All right ♪
- ♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ All right ♪
She's a dancer.
Table dancer?
No. Come on.
It's ballet.
She's a dancer at the Bolshoi.
- She got a name?
- Yeah, her name's Maize.
Maize? Does Maize know
what you do?
I don't think
I can tell her, Zvi.
Are you serious about her?
Yeah, serious enough
to get out of the game
before she finds out.
There's two ways out
of The Killer's Game, Joseph.
You walk away clean
or you go out on your back.
There's a lot of people
who would like
to see me slabbed.
Still with the headaches?
What did Doc Kagen say?
Still waiting on test results.
You play by the rules.
You never took a mark
that didn't have it coming.
No kids,
no innocent bystanders.
You want to walk.
We can make it happen.
Then I'm out.
I was also thinking I should
get a life insurance policy.
Joe, come on.
Guys like us don't have
life insurance policies.
Do I even have to say it?
We don't need
some claims adjuster
sniffing around our business.
I know. Can you just make
something look good on paper?
Fake it. For Maize.
Very well.
And, uh, I got a favor to ask.
- Oh, now there's a favor.
- Yeah.
So Maize wants to have
a birthday dinner for me
and I told her
I'd invite friends.
I thought you and Sharon
might want to...
Yeah.
- Be delighted.
- All right. Thank you.
Uh-uh.
S'il vous plait!
- Maize.
- Yes?
I've known Joseph
for 20 years.
He's the most private person
I know.
And I know this.
He's crazy about you.
- Trust me, it's mutual.
- Right.
Men need looking after
in every area of their lives.
They don't know it,
but they do.
You need to be
a chef in his kitchen,
an accountant with the books,
a lady in the streets,
and a freak in his bed!
Sharon, Sharon.
Don't be a shonda.
Please leave
the poor girl alone.
No, Zvi.
I'm taking notes, please.
- Sharon, anything else?
- Yeah!
Why are you encouraging her?
It makes her happy. Look.
If you've done something bad,
wrecked his motor...
- Okay.
- ...give him a blow job!
If it's really bad, swallow.
And if it's
really, really bad,
let him pop it
in the tradesman's.
Did you just tell me
to take it in the ass?
- Bless.
- She did.
After that,
you can tell him
you've murdered
their mother...
- Right.
- ...cut her throat.
They won't care.
What'd I miss?
Oh, Joe.
Sharon was just giving me
- some very insightful advice.
- Uh-oh.
- I'll show you later.
- Okay.
- Maybe. If you want.
- Joseph...
We are surrounded.
I surrender.
- I surrender with you.
- Yes?
- We give up.
- We surrender.
I can see
why you're retiring.
Boychik, if you're
getting serious with Maize
tell her what you do.
All of it.
I told Sharon everything
very early on.
If Maize loves you,
she'll understand.
You played by the rules.
Women respect integrity.
If she finds out later,
the trust you built,
it's gone.
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪...to you ♪
I forgot it was your birthday.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Oh, man.
♪ Happy birthday, dear Joe ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Wait, make a wish.
Make a wish.
Okay.
We got the results
from those tests.
I'm afraid
I've got some bad news, Joe.
You have
Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease.
It's a neurodegenerative
disorder.
Which means what exactly?
It means rapid
motor-neuron disintegration
leading to a loss
of coordination.
Severe headaches, blindness,
and diminished
mental capacity.
- Are you positive?
- Yeah.
I had the sample tested
by three separate labs
and I got the same result.
Now, I'm going
to order some more tests.
Okay.
So what am I looking at?
Chemo? Something like that?
Hm.
There is no cure.
The first step should be to
get you into palliative care
and the sooner
we begin treatment,
the more comfortable
we can make this for you,
okay?
How long do I have?
Best case, three months.
Things will
deteriorate quickly,
but there are things we can do
to make it easier.
Turn me into a vegetable
while I wait to die.
I don't think so. No.
If you need some therapy,
some counseling...
No.
No, I'm good.
From my end,
Joe, I'm really sorry.
I really am.
"CJD early symptoms, anxiety,
depression, loss of balance,
"speech impairments,
"involuntary movement,
shaking hands..."
Shit!
Joseph.
I wasn't expecting you.
Are you okay?
You look kind of...
I need someone retired.
I need a nice, clean job.
What? What is...
Sorry, what's the matter
with you?
Who's getting retired?
Me.
I'm the target.
I'll pay. Don't worry.
The going rate, two million.
Can you explain to me
exactly what is going on?
I got a disease.
You know, the headaches.
I'm... I'm getting
the shakes and...
and it's gonna take me out.
Here's a little
over a half a million
in mixed currency
and gold coins.
I want you
to liquidate everything else.
It all goes to Maize
through the life insurance.
No, Joseph. This is madness.
The life insurance won't
pay out for a suicide.
She has to believe it.
So I'll pay you
to assign an assassin.
You choose who.
No.
This is what we do.
We go to every doctor.
If they say it's hopeless,
we go up the mountain,
find a shaman.
Zvi...
I've lived by the sword.
I want to go out the same way.
You want to fight,
you fight for your life.
I can't fight if I'm blind...
staggering around
like a drunk, shitting myself.
I don't want Maize
to see me like that.
You know what I think?
I think you want
to protect her from the truth
of who you really are.
Zvi, I'm asking you
for your help.
- I'd do the same for you.
- That's some comfort. Thanks.
It's what I've decided.
I'll see your wishes
are carried out
to the very last dot.
But get one thing straight.
There is no way
on this fucking earth
I'm ordering a hit on you.
Not for two million,
not for 22 million.
Thank you.
What brings Joe Flood
to my door?
I need a contract executed.
Go talk to your rabbi.
I did.
He turned me down.
Conflict of interest.
Joe, if you were covered
in napalm burning alive
I wouldn't piss on you
to put you out.
Perfect.
I've come to the right place.
Max, you know Joe Flood, right?
Best assassin in Europe.
Joe, do you know
my bodyguard, Max?
Hiring war criminals
as security? Classy.
Flood here
handcuffed my father
to the steering wheel
of his Mercedes,
drove him into the sea.
He was a good assassin,
but your father transgressed.
He broke
the rules of the game.
I should have Max put one
in your head right now.
Mon plaisir.
Wait a few hours, Max,
and earn your two million.
You're talking in riddles.
Who do you want retired?
Me.
All these years,
you couldn't touch me
because I was always
on the right side of the game.
Now I'm paying you
for the green light.
Why not do it yourself?
Maybe this was a mistake.
I'm sorry to waste your time.
No, no, no.
Please, sit down.
Two million?
I want it done clean.
My account in Bermuda.
- I know you're good for it.
- Who are you thinking of?
Honestly, it depends
on who's available.
But they'll be the very best.
- Thank you.
- The pleasure's mine.
I've thought about
doing this for years.
Might have risked it
if it wasn't
professional suicide.
This way,
I kill you and get paid.
It gets me wet.
Whatever turns you on.
Give me till 2400 hours.
The clock starts at midnight.
You're the client, Mr. Flood.
Hmm.
Now, who's available
in the Assassin app?
Mm.
♪ Shoot 'em 'for he run now ♪
♪ Do the jerk, baby ♪
♪ Do the jerk now
Hey! ♪
♪ Put on your red dress ♪
♪ And then
you go downtown now ♪
I appreciate the help, brother.
But I got to show receipts.
♪ I said it's twine time ♪
♪ I said it's twine time
Hey! ♪
What? Two mil for Joe Flood?
With inflation
at motherfucking 6%?
Hard pass.
Boo, Lovedahl. Aw.
Then Korean barbeque with
a side of spicy Hungarian.
Mm.
♪ Do you really want
to hurt me? ♪
to make me cry? ♪
♪ Precious kisses
Words that burn me ♪
♪ Lovers never ask you why ♪
♪ In my heart
the fire is burning ♪
♪ Choose my color
Find a star ♪
♪ Do you really want
to hurt me? ♪
to make me cry? ♪
♪ Do you really want
to hurt me? ♪
♪ That's a step
a step too far ♪
♪ Do you really want
to hurt me? ♪
to make me cry? ♪
Huh?
Yeah!
Hey! Delivery request!
- Two million!
- That's real money.
Let's split!
Hey.
Gotcha.
- Hi!
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
- Are you having headaches?
- Yeah.
What's going on?
You're tired?
You seem anxious.
I have to tell you something.
I've got to tell you
something too.
I have to leave town
for a few weeks.
I'm not sure I'm coming back.
What?
That...
What does that mean?
I need to take a step back
and reassess
what I really want.
You're talking crazy.
We make each other happy.
No, we need a break.
A break means
breaking up, Joe.
What is going on?
I know when I love someone,
and I know when they love me.
So what is there
to back away from?
- It's over, Maize.
- What?
It has to be.
Soon this will all
make perfect sense.
Why? Why?
I'm sorry.
Here. Remember me this way.
When you're on your deathbed,
remember what you had
and what you threw away.
I will.
♪ Are you ready, let's go ♪
♪ Are you ready? ♪
Maize, I'm drunk
but I'm speaking the truth.
By the time you get this,
I'll be gone.
Maize, by the time
you get this, I'll be gone.
By the time you get this,
I'll be gone.
Yeah.
Maize...
I'm drunk right now, but...
I want you to know
that I'm speaking the truth.
By the time you get this,
I'll be gone.
I've got Creutzfeldt...
I can't even say it, Maize.
I've got a brain disorder
and it's gonna kill me.
Maize, the only thing
I want you to understand
is it's you I've been
looking for my entire life.
You make me free.
You make me...
You make me feel...
Shit.
Maize...
I'm drunk right now, but...
I want you to know
that I'm speaking the truth.
Oh, Flood. Thank God.
There's been a mistake.
You do not have
Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease.
But they tested me
multiple times.
Yeah, they switched labels
with another patient
and that poor bastard
definitely has
Creutzfeldt-Jakob.
It was the wrong barcode
on the wrong test tube.
I think you should consider
a lawsuit against the lab.
What about my headaches
and double vision?
It's a bit of a mystery.
Have you had
your eyes checked?
- My eyes?
- Flood,
you're not going to die.
In fact, there's nothing
on earth to stop you
from leading
a long and healthy life,
so go and do it.
Give me till 2400 hours.
The clock starts at midnight.
Uh, Doc, I'm gonna
have to call you back.
♪ Are you ready, let's go ♪
Ah.
Goyang, this was a mistake.
I'm canceling the contract.
Fuck you!
That's not how it works!
Mm.
You should've walked.
I got you.
Sorry,
my Korean's a little rusty.
You're calling
from Heaven or Hell?
Goyang's been retired.
I'm canceling the contract.
Love to oblige,
but events have gathered
a momentum of their own.
I'll pay a penalty charge.
I'll take a hit.
You're going to take a hit.
Look, keep the two mil.
Just cancel the contract.
I'm obligated to see to it
that the client's wishes
are met.
Yeah, I'm the client,
and I'm telling you to cancel.
That's only if this phone call
ever happened.
You killed my father,
and he loved you like the son
he never had.
Let me tell you something
about your father.
I couldn't stand that prick.
Antoinette, I don't
often enjoy my work
but that one,
that was a real pleasure.
You think a Korean barbeque
changes anything?
It changes nothing!
I'm sending this one out wide.
I'm calling in every hitter
in Europe,
you hear me?
I'm calling in
every motherfucking killer
with a shiv
from Istanbul to Dublin!
Yeah. Well, you tell them
to pack light
because they won't fucking
be staying long.
Hello, leave me
a message.
Maize, I'm in trouble.
I'll explain to you
when I see you.
It's not safe for you
to go home.
I'm gonna send you some money.
Use it
to go wherever you want.
Just get out of Budapest.
And don't tell me
where you're going.
I'll find you. Wherever
you go, wherever you are,
I will find you. I swear it.
And stay off your phone.
Guess who, motherfucker!
- Hey, Zoli.
- Hey, Flood.
Where's your dumbass brother?
He's right behind you.
You serve, I spike!
One point!
Hey, bro, serve it up!
Hey, Flood! This is business.
Nothing personal.
You know
how the game works, Flood.
Yeah, I know how it works.
That was business.
This is personal.
Zoli!
You bastard!
- That was my brother!
- One!
Come on!
- Come on!
- Fuck you!
Putain.
I'm going to expand
the field of vendors.
How wide?
Double Supreme.
That's going
to be expensive.
When I want your opinion,
I'll tell you.
I'll spend my own money.
Don't care what cutthroats
crawl out the woodwork.
I want Joe Flood dead.
Now go wash your ass.
I'll be there in a minute.
♪ Hot pants lady ♪
♪ I dig your style ♪
♪ You blow my cool
when you come walking by ♪
♪ Hot pants lady ♪
♪ You're right on time ♪
Halle-fucking-lujah!
Four fucking million
motherfucking dollars!
All right, ladies.
The show's over.
Get your asses moving.
Daddy's gotta go to work.
The party's over?
"We don't have tomorrow,
but we sure had yesterday."
Diana Ross, baby girl.
Now, you ain't gotta go home
but you got to get the hell
out of here.
Let's fucking go!
♪ Wild thing ♪
♪ You make my heart sing ♪
♪ You make everything groovy ♪
♪ Hey, oh, oh, wild thing ♪
♪ Wild thing ♪
♪ I think I love you ♪
♪ But I wanna know for sure ♪
♪ Come on and hold me tight ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Wild thing ♪
♪ You make everything groovy ♪
♪ Hey, oh, wild thing ♪
♪ Wild thing... ♪
- Another delivery.
- In Budapest.
Just as well.
This party is dead.
♪ You make everything groovy ♪
♪ Hey, oh, oh, wild thing ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Ole! ♪
Maize, I'm in trouble.
I'll explain to you
when I see you.
It's not safe for you
to go home. I'm gonna
- send you some money.
- What?
Use it to go
wherever you want.
Just get out of Budapest.
Don't tell me where you're going.
I'll find you.
Wherever you go,
wherever you are,
I will find you. I swear.
Quick, get inside.
I've been expecting you.
- You weren't followed?
- No.
Oy gevalt, look at you.
Who is it, Zvi?
It's Joseph, Sharon.
Go to sleep.
- Does he know what time it is?
- Yes, dear. He owns a watch.
Should I make him
something to eat?
Hey, Sharon. No, thanks.
Kinda lost my appetite.
Let's get you fixed up.
You were on the news.
Five dead Koreans.
Yeah. They came at me
at 12:00 on the dot.
You went to Antoinette's?
- Yeah, you said no.
- I said, "Fight."
The doctors fucked up.
You were right.
What do they know?
I'm gonna live.
I'd say that's up
in the air right now.
Yeah, she's still angry
about her old man.
Some people
take things so personal.
There's only one way
out of this.
You kill Antoinette,
that's a violation.
She's simply facilitating
your own stupid request.
No, I want her
to think I'm running.
I'm gonna bring them all
into one place
and take them all out.
She'll have to lift
the contract.
She put
the call out wide.
Double Supreme.
Double Supreme?
I only gave her two mil.
She's serious
about delivering.
Zvi, that bag of cash,
you gotta get that to Maize.
And I'm gonna need a gun.
Well, I don't have one here.
Joseph, I schedule retirements
these days.
I don't actually
make them happen.
You don't have anything?
Oh, man.
Explosives? That's it?
Leftover from the Mehrabi job.
That was you?
Fourteen personal bodyguards,
the entire Moroccan Police
and the French DGSE
watching his back
and he asks, "Was that you?"
Wow.
All right. Well, if we're
gonna bring them all to me,
we gotta be slick.
They can't think it's a setup.
Please.
I was dropping the KGB
onto false trails
when you were getting trapped
by training bras.
I've got salt beef.
You like salt beef.
- Now, don't say you don't.
- I do love salt beef.
So, where?
You remember that place
where we held
the diplomat's son?
Mmm.
- Speak.
- I'll keep it brief.
Flood took out a contract
on his own life.
Classy.
He's making it a lot harder
on everyone than he should.
The brother is intractable.
Flood has a girlfriend.
I'm gonna send some data.
Nice. The man has taste.
Make sure he doesn't
leave Budapest alive.
I'm giving you an edge.
In exchange,
I need a little favor.
Your driver, he's my cousin.
I'm trying to mentor him
into the business.
I promised my late uncle.
Could you look after him?
He's a bit green.
I'd appreciate it.
For you, mistress,
but he mustn't cramp my style.
I'm working.
Gros bisous.
Yo!
You my man, The Lovedog!
It's Lovedahl.
Love. Dahl.
Practice repeatedly.
Like Dahl.
Like curry and dem, man.
Yeah, yeah. I hear that.
You cannot
be Queen Bitch's cousin.
Yeah, bruv! I be dem Money,
and this be your ride, G.
I asked for a luxury car.
I don't even know
what the fuck that is.
Yeah, bruv. No, this
a luxury car, man. It's a BM.
Take my shit and let's go.
You want me to take your bag?
Take my shit...
- and get in the fucking car!
- Yeah, it's cool.
Man, jump in the car,
I'll cut the AC
and that long journey, bruv.
You relax, man.
This is a heavy bag.
It's expensive, too.
Damn, it smells
like fish in here.
It's dank cologne, bruv.
Shut this shit off!
Stop, Sharon.
You'll kill the poor man.
You'll snap his neck.
I know what I'm doing.
You met me
in a massage parlor.
I didn't go there
for a massage.
Yeah, well...
that's your mistake.
You've paralyzed
the poor man.
Oh, my God.
I can see clearly.
My headache's gone!
Sharon, you're a saint!
You're a s... Oh, my God!
- Joseph. Joe...
- Oh, my God!
I'll never hear the end of it.
You're welcome.
Fucking gold, bruv!
Wicked track,
filthy bars, yeah?
I thought I told you
to turn that shit off?
All right.
Make it all sad and that
in here,
real tense and that.
So you want in the game?
Hell, yeah, bruv. Yeah, man.
- Of course.
- Why?
They don't call me "Money"
for no reason, G.
Make them stacks, yeah.
There's a lot of ways
to make money.
But this shit here,
it's an artform.
- A calling.
- Yeah, mate.
I've been training for this
all my life.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Guns, knives, Muay Thai, JKD.
I'm hard as nails, bruv.
I'm stone cold motherfucker!
- Give me that.
- But that's...
Before you shoot
your dick off.
That's my strap still, bruv.
All right. Cool.
Yeah, bruv, listen, see.
Man, me and you, yeah,
we can be like
the new dynamic duo, yeah?
You know, like Eminem
and 50 Cent, bruv.
Starsky and Hutch.
You know?
Like Crockett and Tubbs.
We could be like the guys
from Miami Vice.
We could be
the Corleone brothers.
Shut the fuck up, will you?
Just a minute, please.
Ooh.
You done good-good, Flood.
Hey, who are you
staring at, bruv?
Shut the fuck up, please.
Please.
Joe.
Who are you?
Hey, now, baby girl.
I'm an old friend
of Joe Flood's.
He sent me to collect you.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Now, this is way too public
for the conversation
we need to have.
Yeah, see, we got a whip
waiting for you, sister.
We're gonna take you
to see Mr. Flood.
Oh, shit!
Goddamn!
Fucking hell!
Get in the car!
And stop fucking
bleeding everywhere!
Fucking hell. You good, yeah?
All right.
You were right.
His old handler
is trying to set up an out.
Where?
Some old castle
on the mountain road
between here and Prague.
For sure?
He tried to hide it all,
but his tech isn't quite
as good as ours.
Zvi stopped with tech
around the time
the digital clock
was invented.
Maximilious,
notify the hitters
and call up your mercenaries.
Joe Flood might think he can
hold off a few assassins
but he can't fight
an army too.
Oh, fuck me!
Here we go.
Location update.
Schatzberger Castle.
It's a fucking stupid name,
isn't it?
- How's the drive?
- Scenic.
Your plan worked.
Antoinette posted
the change of location.
- It's a free-for-all.
- Four million for all.
Nobody in my stable
will touch it,
even for four million.
You must be loved.
Your old friend Lovedahl
took the bait.
Four million
buys a lot of vinyl.
Sweetheart, what do you really
know about Flood?
That he's kind and gentle.
Gentle?
Your lover-man has been,
for the last 20 years,
the most prolific
professional hitman in Europe.
You need a job done right,
give it to Joe.
Joe Flood,
more hits than Motown.
Then you better hope
he doesn't find you.
Baby girl...
I got four million reasons
why I need him to.
Mm.
Come on.
Shh!
What's the matter?
Things slow at the pub?
Filthy dog!
Angus!
Come on!
What's that smell?
Let's smash the cunt!
The cable's kinked, brother!
That's right!
Bullseye, you bastard!
It's gonna be like that here?
Yeah, come on!
Incoming!
Fuck!
It looks like
the party's already started.
Shit.
I forgot the gifts.
No, we didn't.
Ah, nice work, brother!
Jesus, what'd you kick me for?
I kicked you
so that I could kick him.
- You were in the way.
- I bloody had him,
- and you ruined it!
- You had him?
- Thank you very much!
- Finish him off then!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Mess with the bull...
Fuck!
...you get the horn.
Angus! I've got
a serious itch here.
You'll be all right, Rory.
It's just a scratch, lad.
Fuck.
Rory! Fuck!
That's my brother
you just killed.
You're gonna pay for that,
you fucking twat!
Showtime!
Hey, Flood! I heard you're
looking for a good time.
How about a little G&T?
Appreciate the offer,
but that's not my drink.
Oh, we cater
to everyone's tastes, baby.
Maybe a lap dance, instead?
Oh, Flood,
you're such a tease!
Shot your wad, big boy?
I hate to see you go,
but I love to watch you leave.
Bloody hell!
Hey, Botas.
(DON'T LET ME BE MISUNDERSTOOD
BY SANTA ESMERALDA,
♪ Baby, do you
understand me now? ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel
a little mad ♪
♪ But don't you know
that no one alive ♪
♪ Can always be an angel ♪
♪ When things go wrong,
I seem to be bad ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm just a soul
whose intentions are good ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, please don't
let me be misunderstood ♪
♪ Well, if I get edgy,
I want you to know ♪
♪ That I never meant
to take it out on you ♪
♪ Life has its problems
And I've got my share ♪
♪ But that's one thing... ♪
♪ I never meant to do ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Baby, don't you know
I'm just human ♪
♪ And I've got faults
like any other man ♪
♪ And sometimes I... ♪
Slow your roll.
Huh?
Whoo! She got
la-di-da-di everybody here.
Roll on down there and
slide up on that right flank.
What's a flank, bruv?
Just go on down there.
What, like this way
on the right?
- On the right.
- Right. Okay.
Tell me what you see.
Big fucking house, yo!
What you're seeing is a trap.
Anyone goes in that building
looking for Joe Flood
ain't getting out.
Yeah, that makes sense, bruv.
So how do we get in?
You stay here in the rear.
Don't let her
get away from you.
Who? Oh, her?
Yeah, bruv. No drama, man.
No mas Botas.
- Maize?
- Sorry, wish it were.
- Lovedahl.
- Yeah, man.
Where's Maize?
I thought I'd bring her along
for the ride.
It's nice to leave the city
this time of year.
- If you hurt her...
- I don't want to.
All I want to do is collect,
but you have my word.
You get through all that,
present your big ass to me,
and I will let
your little ballerina here go.
You feel me?
- Me for her?
- That's the real real.
Can I get a little help?
Come on, brother.
That would be unethical.
- And kidnapping my woman?
- I'm morally flexible.
Is that another term
for asshole?
Looks like you got
some more guests arriving.
Coming through
the graveyard to the east.
I'm gonna kill
that fucking doctor, too!
"Have you had
your eyes checked?"
The plans show there's
an entrance down this way.
Take your men down there
and secure the catacombs.
We'll go in through the front
and flush him out.
- Yes, sir.
- You three, come with me.
Yes, sir.
Go.
♪ I can move with the beat ♪
♪ I could move on the street ♪
♪ And I'm comfy
like that, bud ♪
- Hey, my legs are asleep.
- So?
Just let me
walk around a minute?
And do you know what?
You really
embarrassed me before.
I'm trying
to get into the game,
and my first job, wham!
Thumped by a ballet dancer.
Come on, just let me
get the blood flow going!
And do you know what?
No, no, no.
You caught me
by surprise before, yeah?
This black nose
wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry I hit you.
All right, so if I let you
out the car now,
you're not gonna run?
You're not gonna go anywhere?
You're just gonna chill.
Where am I gonna go?
No. I'm gonna chill.
I just need to get
the blood flow going.
- Yeah?
- All right.
We're at a bit of a stall,
jump out the fucking car then.
- Now come out the whip, man.
- One second.
You were so eager
to get out of the car,
now you don't want to move.
You want help?
Yeah, all right. Take my hand.
Dickhead.
And stay there. Don't run off.
Hard to kill.
Like Springsteen live,
you do not disappoint.
You've seen The Boss live?
Meadowlands, 1997,
but his Broadway show
was truly special.
Where's Maize?
Me for her. That's the deal.
Lose the shotgun.
I'm gonna call my associate
and have her
brought down here.
You should've
told her the truth, Flood.
What do you know about that?
What don't I know about
a woman's heart, brother?
I didn't think that was
the part of their anatomy
you'd be interested in.
You got me all wrong.
Get in the car!
I got her.
How the hell
the bitch get your car?
She hit me with a branch.
A branch?
How'd she get
a fucking branch?
I... I let her out of the car
just for a minute, and then...
- You dumbass fucking wannabe.
- Sorry, Mr. Lovedahl, sir.
Sorry, uh, really strong.
Um...
I just want to say
that I don't really think
that I'm cut out
for this kind of work, sir.
That might be
the first intelligent thing
I've heard you say.
- So, now what?
- The contract is still active.
Oh, I'm not splitting my money
with you, Sly
and the Family Stone here.
We're mercenaries.
We already got paid.
Now this is some bullshit.
You tell Queen Bitch
if she still wants him dead,
the price is going up.
Yeah, to what?
- Six million.
- Six million?
I gotta make a call.
Do you think I killed him?
I hope so.
What? No. Joe.
No, I don't think you did.
But I don't think
it felt great.
Good.
The night we met,
the men who died...
- Yeah, that was me.
- That was opening night!
I'm sorry.
And how about
the last 24 hours, Joe?
Do you have
an explanation for that?
- Or some bullshit apologies?
- No.
- I thought I was dying.
- What?
I hired an old enemy
to take me out clean.
It turns out
I was misdiagnosed.
- What?
- I tried to protect you.
Protect me from who?
A bunch of killers or you?
Both! From all of it.
What do you do for a living?
Huh?
- Maize, I'm a hitman.
- You kill people?
Well, I'm retired from that.
- You look it.
- I'm retiring.
You're a murderer for hire!
That's what
an assassin is, yeah.
I don't know
if it'll make any difference
but the people I work for,
we don't kill civilians,
just criminals.
Well, that's what
you've been doing.
- You're retired.
- Yes.
Good, because I'm not
having a kid with a killer.
A kid?
I'm pregnant, Joe.
I tried to tell you
the other night
but you broke up with me.
Look, I love you, you love me,
and the rest we'll figure out
as we go, okay?
I swear,
I'll never lie to you again.
Are you okay?
- You better fucking not...
- Hey. Maize?
Jeez.
Shit. You caught one.
Maize. Maize.
Come on, breathe.
Stay with me.
Maize.
Perhaps I can be
of some assistance?
Not unless you're a doctor.
Do I look like a doctor?
Is there one in the village?
There's a half decent vet.
The nearest doctor
- is 40 kilometers away.
- Maize.
Hey, baby. Are you okay?
Joe.
Baby.
Easy.
You got shot.
It hurts.
It just grazed you.
I thought
I was gonna lose you.
You're gonna have to try
harder than that.
Maize, I love you.
Will you marry me?
- What?
- Marry me.
Be my wife.
To have and to hold,
sickness and health,
the whole thing.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Father, will you marry us?
Do you have
a marriage license?
No.
- Do you have any witnesses?
- You.
Are you even Catholic?
I think my mother was.
Oh. So it's guilt
by association.
Look, Father, in the last day
I've had more people try
to kill me than I can count,
and I just found out
I'm gonna be a father.
So I might not get
another shot at this,
so what do you say?
On one condition.
Yeah, name it.
You must give confession.
Ooh.
I don't think we have
that kind of time, Father.
Make time.
Oh, man.
So that brings us up
to the last couple months.
Um...
There was a chief
of a Corsican crime syndicate.
That was one shot
over a mile out.
A Romanian arms dealer.
Uh, did him
at close range with a pistol.
A rogue British agent
in Geneva.
That was hand-to-hand...
A Russian oligarch in Vienna,
a garrote.
I mean, real quiet.
In all my years as a priest,
as a human being,
I have never heard
anything remotely...
And last night, there was
the entire Goyang crew.
They came after me,
so technically, self-defense.
Murder is murder is murder.
No technicalities.
Most of my targets
never saw it coming.
Kind of a point of pride
with top hitmen.
Pride is a sin.
Well, kind of lightweight
compared to contract killing, right?
I'm not sure I'm qualified
to pardon all of this.
What, do you need to call
the Vatican or something?
They'd tell me
to call the police.
Look, Father.
The way I see it is your boss,
the man upstairs,
he's given me a second chance.
I'm gonna be a father,
so I don't want
to mess that up.
I'll give you redemption,
but no more killing,
no more murder.
Well, there might be some
self-defense in the near future.
Do you get this?
It's a sin. It's wrong.
You asked for a confession.
I wish I kept my mouth shut
if we're both being honest here.
So are you gonna marry us now,
or what?
Ego te absolvo. I absolve you.
All right. Thank you, Father.
Dearly beloved,
you're gathered here today
in the presence of God
to declare
your love, honor, fidelity,
and commitment to one another
for as long
as you both shall live.
I don't suppose
you have a ring, do you?
Um... Oh!
Will this do?
As long as the grenade
is far away.
It went off hours ago.
One of the party girls.
I lost track. Silly me.
Back to the wedding.
Do you, Joe, take this woman
to love, honor and obey
in sickness and in health
for as long as you shall live?
I do.
And do you, Maize,
take this man
to love, honor, and obey?
- I don't know about obey.
- Maize!
I object!
You couldn't have waited
30 seconds?
You done made this shit
hard enough!
Shit!
I got this!
I don't think so!
The boss said,
"Fuck your six million!"
The game's changed,
my brother!
Okay. Easy. All right.
Okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
All right.
Keep pressure on that.
- Wait, Joe.
- I gotta finish this.
Flood!
You know how this goes.
It's not personal.
It's strictly business.
I don't know about you, Flood,
but I'm taking this
mighty personally.
I ain't dead yet,
motherfucker!
I've seen fights at weddings.
This is not like that.
Who are you people?
- I got shot.
- I know.
After giving confession.
Like horseshoes
and hand grenades, baby!
Come on!
This is what you wanted,
isn't it?
That's enough.
They're breaking my church.
Flood!
Just come on out, baby!
I'll kill you quick,
I promise.
Fuck!
Tell me, Flood.
You really think there's
a happily ever after
for guys like us?
You think you're just
gonna walk out of here,
go home and play house?
The boss is never
going to stop, Flood.
You'll have
to kill that bitch, too.
Help, help me, boss...
He wasn't gonna make it.
I'm a professional.
You guys come
right out of a comic book.
Unlucky.
You know, there are only
two ways out of the game.
You walk away clean,
or you go out on your...
Or you go out on your back.
Hey. It's okay.
- Are you okay?
- He... He was going to...
I know. It's okay.
You did good.
- Should we finish him?
- No. I'm retired.
Y'all make a cute couple,
but don't leave
a brother hanging.
Come on, Flood!
Get me out of here!
Really?
Come on, man!
Maybe you should
retire too.
Y'all don't leave me here!
Fuck this.
You know better
than to run.
Your boy
hasn't left me any choice.
There's only two ways
out of the game, Antoinette.
Who put the contract on me?
You did.
You hired mercenaries
on a contract job.
Just like your father,
you broke the rules.
Fuck you, and fuck the rules!
Don't hate the player...
hate the game.
♪ Get back! ♪
- ♪ Payback! ♪
- ♪ The big payback! ♪
♪ That's it ♪
♪ Payback! ♪
♪ I'm mad! ♪
♪ You get down
with my girlfriend ♪
♪ That ain't right... ♪
The funds
for the church renovation
are much appreciated, Joe.
Well, I did play a hand
in wrecking it
in the first place.
Acceptance is the beginning
of deliverance.
- How's your shoulder?
- It fucking hurts.
What kind of ring
do you call that?
Yeah,
what kind of ring is that?
Tactical?
- Tactical, yeah. Tactique.
- Tactical.
- Mm.
- En francais.
Merci.
You know,
if you're ever short,
with Antoinette gone
and every decent hitter
in Europe out of the game,
I'm going to have more work
than I can manage.
- I'm retired.
- No, he's retired.
I just wanted
to hear him say it.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Look after him.
So handsome.
Thank you.
He's retired.
You know we're
gonna have to start saving
for a college fund.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, how much would you get
to just, like, hurt somebody?
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
Um, well, college isn't cheap,
but first there's daycare,
of course.
Diapers are crazy expensive.
Baby formula
is even more expensive.
Oh, and we're gonna need
one of those baskets.
- Baskets? Okay.
- Baskets. Yeah. Oh...
♪ So, brother, get ready ♪
♪ That's a fact! ♪
♪ Get ready, you mother! ♪
♪ For the big payback ♪
- ♪ The big payback! ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Let me hit 'em
Hit 'em, Fred, hit 'em ♪
♪ Hey, hey! Whoo! ♪
♪ Lord! ♪
♪ You took my money ♪
♪ You got my honey ♪
♪ Don't want me to see
what you doing to me ♪
♪ I gotta get back ♪
♪ I gotta deal with you ♪
♪ Gotta deal with ya ♪
♪ I! ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ Get down with my woman ♪
♪ That ain't right! ♪
♪ You hollerin' and cussin' ♪
♪ You wanna fight! ♪
♪ Look here! ♪
♪ Don't do me... ♪
♪ No darn favor ♪
♪ I don't know karate ♪
- ♪ But I know ka-razor ♪
- ♪ Yes, we do! ♪
♪ Huh! ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Get ready! ♪
♪ That's a fact, yeah! ♪
♪ Get ready, you mother! ♪
♪ For the big payback ♪
♪ The big payback! ♪
♪ All right ♪