THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS
The Joseon Dynasty scholar Jeong Yeo-rip
asserted that all people are equal
and should have no master.
In a private community he formed
called Great Unity,
noblemen and slaves shared food and drink
and practiced martial arts together.
Accused of treason
and besieged by the king's army,
Jeong Yeo-rip took his own life
by plunging a sword into his neck.
This was under the reign of King Seonjo.
Get the captives ready!
I say all kings
and all slaves
are born equal.
"Are born equal?"
SEONJEONGJEON HALL
Is this a message from your father?
Answer me now.
How can he answer with his tongue cut out?
- Quiet.
- I believe he had much to say.
"The world belongs to all."
"Whoever wants the throne may take it."
Councilor!
"Kings and slaves are equals, you see."
Is that how things are?
My liege!
Do not sully your royal lips
with the words of that traitor!
Butchers, whores, slaves,
all of them could…
could occupy the throne if that's true.
Sit down if you want.
Ah, the gonryongpo.
- Of course, how could I forget?
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
I beg you, Your Majesty!
We beg you, Your Majesty.
How could such a horrible thing happen?!
Judge! What are you waiting for?
Cut the heads off the disgusting traitors
and hang them high!
OK-NAM, SON OF REBEL LEADER JEONG YEO-RIP
Gather round!
Here we go once more!
Did you see that?
You see that?
Let me try one more time.
One more time.
Oh, how horrible.
Runaway slave!
Make way! Runaway slave!
Look at this. This is what happens
when slaves try to run!
Hey, look. Up there. You see that?
Just like a certain someone,
he stepped out of line,
and look how that ended, huh?
Bastard!
What's happening here?
Such insolence!
Inspector-General Yi Deok-hyeong is here!
Show some respect!
- Let go of me!
- Hey, keep still!
In such close proximity
to our royal highness…
- Let go of me!
- …must you really raise such a fuss?
Please forgive me for my impudence,
my lord.
I'm a slave hunter. My name is Gwang-yi.
So far, I've managed
to capture this many slaves.
He's made a run for it twice now.
He's rotten to the core.
RUNAWAY SLAVE
And this time, he even stole
something priceless from his master.
This is our master's sword.
YI JONG-RYEO
BEST IN MILITARY ARTS
His mother was a slave
of the Deputy Minister of Defense.
12 YEARS AGO
JANGYEWON: SLAVE REGISTRY OFFICE
Like one, like all.
Do you know what this means?
I believe it means
a child with a slave parent
is consigned to a life of slavery as well.
That's the law, I'm afraid. Case closed.
But my wife and I were both born
as common folk.
She was sold off
so our debt could be paid,
but… my son was conceived
before any of that happened.
But is a child not
part of a mother's body?
When the mother becomes a slave,
then so does the child inside.
That can only be right.
He was raised free,
and now suddenly he's a slave?
Give me that.
- Look, you little…
- Ah! No! Don't!
My father made that for me!
You disobedient…
I'm going to teach you the history
of the family you'll be serving,
so clean out your ears and listen.
I really don't care.
You will be working for the family
of the esteemed
Deputy Minister of Defense.
Ever since King Taejo's reign,
the men in his family have always passed
the national military exam.
They are the most influential family
in Joseon.
Their mansion has more than 60 rooms.
The family owns more than
a hundred noh-bi.
"Noh" means male slave.
"Bi" means female slave.
And each slave has
a different task to perform.
♪ The letter bearer delivers mail ♪
♪ The broomboy sweeps the yard ♪
♪ Cooks prepare all the meals ♪
♪ While steamers make the rice ♪
♪ Laundresses wash clothes
While water bearers work the well ♪
♪ The stoker builds fires ♪
♪ Shovelers clean the outhouse ♪
♪ The woodcutter cuts firewood ♪
♪ The stablehand feeds the horses ♪
♪ Empty the chamber's pots, mop the floor
Iron the clothes, sew the stitches ♪
♪ Dress the young master
Give the madam a massage ♪
♪ Fan the master and wash his feet
So many slaves, so many jobs ♪
Among all those tasks,
can you guess what yours is?
Swing it!
I'll be whipped in his stead? Why?
Well,
you're the young master's body servant.
Why wouldn't you be whipped in his stead?
He's going to be a general.
He can't be covered in scars.
How does that make sense?
- What's this now?
- Why would I get hit?
- I didn't do anything.
- Shut up, will you?
You talk too much for a little brat.
Ah! We are back, Master.
Bow your head, now!
- Do you even realize where…
- Hmm?
You rascal!
Come here!
- You little shit!
- Enough of this!
Get rid of it!
My baby!
He's got strong bones.
Healthy as an ox. Look at these teeth.
See? All of them are there.
This is the new boy?
I'm curious how long this one will last.
How can I go on after this?
How could this happen?
It's my fault, darling.
It's my fault you were born a slave.
Oh God, it's all my fault!
It's inhuman.
How many times has this happened now?
Let's… Let's cover him up now.
Your name is Cheon-yeong?
What does your name mean?
I guess you don't know.
This "Cheon" means "to follow,"
and this "Yeong" means "shadow."
You'll follow me like a shadow.
What do you say?
Ah!
You still have
your baby teeth.
You think I'll be your shadow?
What are you doing?
Huh?
Wait!
I'm back!
Father?
Huh?
Oh shit.
Go away! I said go away!
- Cut it out.
- Father!
- Ooh, you're a loud one.
Keep walking.
Isn't that Cheon-yeong?
Goodness, how many years has it been?
You really can't let go, can you?
Each time I manage to get out,
you drag me right on back.
Just be quiet, will you?
Look how far you've come.
Our young master
who failed the exam every year,
and then, after some miracle, you…
you end up placing first in the nation.
- What does that even mean?
- What'd he say?
Do it.
The servants are watching, Father.
You cannot take his life. Please.
Worthless degenerate.
Lock him in the shed!
Just kill me!
Unless you want your whole family
to die slowly by my hands, Master.
Your father.
Your mother.
Your wife!
Your child.
I'll throw every one of you
into a raging fire
and watch as you die!
Hold him down.
There's nothing I can do for you anymore.
- Your head's exposed.
- He goes high.
Then left, jab,
down to the right, up to the left…
Ah.
Look,
for each time I get hit during the day,
you get hit twice at night.
Get in position.
Your teacher's moves are predictable.
If he starts high up,
he always falls to the right
and then like this.
- If he starts from here--
- The shoulders. He'll jab first.
So you know.
Let's practice, then.
You have to duck under it.
Uh-uh. The other foot.
- Like this?
- Yeah, good work.
Starting tomorrow,
I have to train with you.
Does that mean
he won't hit me anymore, you think?
Uh-huh. I think so.
Strike!
This won't work at the exam, you know.
You have to put in some anger.
You don't need to worry.
Once I meet a real foe,
this sword will… hold plenty of anger.
MILITARY EXAMINATION OFFICE
- Park Tae-ju.
- Here.
- Kim Yi-nam.
Yi Jong-ryeo.
- Wish me luck.
- Yi Jong-ryeo.
Go!
How many failures does this mark?
You shame not only me
but this whole house!
When I die, how will I face my ancestors?
Wait!
Please allow me
to take the exam on Young Master's behalf.
Are you out of your mind?
My only request is that you
promise to liberate me.
Then I shall pass with top marks
and bring home the royal flowers.
- Yi Jong-ryeo.
- I am Yi Jong-ryeo.
- Kim Min-seok.
- Here.
- Yi Jong-won.
Why, Our Majesty even gave him
a cheongchonik.
The royal flowers suit you well,
I have to say.
Not even I placed first.
Can you believe it?
Cheon-yeong.
Look at you.
You were born to wear a cheongchonik.
Wait here.
I'll get your slave papers from Father.
Have a drink in the meantime.
I was told
not to give him a drop of water.
Anyone who disobeys orders
will end up like this.
Get out!
Back to work!
Father, take a look at that bird.
It looks like it's floating.
What in the world is… That looks like…
Oh!
WAR
- Young Master.
- Steward Kim.
- Is Mother still awake?
- Yes.
You say the king will flee the capital?
I, too, must leave now
to escort His Majesty.
I sent a messenger to Uncle in Wonsan.
You must leave quietly
once Father gets back here.
Please take good care of him.
My sword is missing.
I shall find it
and send it to you at once.
So worry not and make haste, Young Master.
The key.
Come on.
How could they already be at Yongin
when Busan Fortress just fell?
Makes no sense to me.
They blew through
General Shin's great army.
A complete disaster.
Why else would we get ready to flee?
Fucking hell.
Sounds like it's no ordinary war.
Oh…
I know you're a lowborn thief,
but still, there are limits.
You dare steal a gift from His Majesty?
Hand it over right now!
- I don't know what you mean!
- How dare you play dumb with me!
- Where's the blade, huh?
- I don't know! I have no idea!
- Give me the damn blade!
- He told you he doesn't know!
You. You dare?!
Everyone take arms.
How long must we be treated like pigs?
Put those down this instant.
What do you think you're doing?
Where are the papers, huh?
You're home awfully late
tonight, my lord.
Look at this. You see this right here?
This means we're equals now.
Now, now, hurry!
Young Master.
No.
The young master, where'd he go?
- Where's your husband?
- Keep away! Stay away from me!
This is your curse, you brute!
This is dangerous. My lady, don't…
No, don't head that…
You dare touch me with those filthy hands!
Are you insane?
Get out of there!
Now even the lanterns fail us.
Come on!
Everyone, carefully now.
Go slowly.
Oh!
Oh no, Your Highness,
are you all right?
- Forgive me.
- Must I lie here in the rain?
Your Highness!
Well, what did she expect
if she wouldn't ride a horse?
Are you all right,
Your Highness?
Oh?
What are you staring at, hmm?
What are you all…
- How could they have reached here already?
- It's impossible.
The Japanese couldn't have
crossed the Han River yet.
Then what am I looking at?
- That is the palace, is it not?
- Yes, sire.
Oh.
I demand to know who would dare
to set the Royal Palace on fire.
Your Majesty, shamefully, I must report
that the people of the city have…
My people did this?
Why would they?
What kind of king deserts
his people and runs?
Give me those goddamn papers!
You fools!
You think this is gonna change anything?
TRAITOR JEONG YEO-RIP
Look at it burn! Burn it all down!
- How could this happen?
- Father, no!
Serves them right!
I thought all the officers
had fled the capital.
The capital, finally.
Forward.
- Forward!
- Yes, sir!
Come!
WEAPONS MANUFACTURING OFFICE
Everybody gather round now!
I hear the Japanese
have crossed the river.
It's just a matter of time now.
Even the king himself has forsaken us.
It's on us to do what we can
to fight back.
We're dying out here.
- Do you have some sort of plan in mind?
- What can we do?
Over here!
Look, I brought you a military officer.
- Oh, it's Sam-mun!
- Who's that next to him?
Is that really an officer?
He looks so shabby.
Look at that sword and robe.
You can tell right away.
Right, right.
Spears, swords, bows!
Can any of you wield these?
Out of all the men here,
is this really it?
All who serve will be rewarded.
Even slaves.
Yes, all of you.
Liberty! Buy yourselves out of slavery.
Do not hesitate because
of your lowborn status. Step forward.
- Anybody. Come on.
- When it comes to slings, I'm unbeatable.
You won't find a better shot.
How about it?
No, no, no, no! Have you lost your mind?
- Are you trying to get killed?
- You said swords.
How about a meat cleaver?
Does that work for ya?
Mr. Butcher, it sure does.
Never in my wildest dreams
could I have imagined
being addressed as "mister."
- Then I'm in too!
- Stop it, you fool!
Come forward, then.
We should see if there are weapons
left over in the armory.
Yeah, come on, let's go! Let's go.
I lack energy. I need to eat.
Quickly, bring a platter.
- Ready the boat.
- Mind your posture.
- Post guards to keep watch.
- Yes, sir.
Don't let a single one live.
Burn it all down!
You dare, you dog?
- Let go!
- Stay still, shaman wench.
Do you not fear
the wrath of heaven?!
What is this, then?
You bastard! I see it.
The blade you carry now
will find itself lodged in your throat.
What did she say?
She said your sword
will end up piercing your throat.
I will pierce my own throat?
I'll remember that.
How will it happen?
Like this?
This is all you bring?
I've never laid my eyes on such fish.
Forgive us, my lord.
We combed through every home in the area,
but this is all we could find.
- What was that?
- Right there.
- Look, there he is!
- Over there, over there!
What the hell is this?
He's right there. Get him!
Bow your heads.
You've bled us dry for years,
and now you abandon us all to die?
We can't even honor our dead.
That fish was for memorial rites.
That was for our families!
- These insolent…
- Do you crave death?
- You dare block the royal path?
- We don't care if the path is royal!
The bastard's leaving us to die
while he rides to safety!
Get His Majesty to the boat!
Let go of me!
- Out of the way!
- You bastard!
Yi Jong-ryeo, what are you doing?
Out of the way!
What are you doing here?
I regret to inform you, sir,
your slaves took up torches
and burned your manor to the ground.
What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Where's my family?
Are they all right?
It was already too late when I arrived.
I fear the fire had already taken them.
And… my son too?
Hey, you sons of bitches!
One more thing.
Cheon-yeong was fleeing the manor,
and he stole your horse.
He was wearing your blue robe.
I want Cheon-yeong brought to me
immediately.
Kill them all!
Are you all right, sir?
Where did that come from?
Bullseye!
Is he alone?
What's that clown
think he's doing?
Whoo!
You son of a…
Oh, I'm gonna get you.
- You bastards!
- This way, you dirty rats!
Get over here!
Shields, forward!
- Get away!
- Chase them!
Not yet. Not yet!
Hold formation! Hold formation!
Fire! Forward!
How reckless.
Some nigirimeshi, sir.
Keep pushing. Don't fall back!
Second line, forward!
Reload!
Hit them
when they're reloading.
- Get ready.
- Huh?
Right, right, right.
Fire!
Aoki.
Break through the right side
with the cavalrymen.
Yes, sir.
Royal Guard Commander,
protect His Majesty!
Damn you!
- Honda.
- Sir!
Your Majesty!
There's no time for that.
Hurry! Hurry! Set sail now!
That's right! That's right.
Launch the boat! Now!
Sir, please, let us live!
Show yourself.
Stand down.
I am Genshin Kikkawa,
Konishi Battalion's frontline commander.
State your rank and name.
This is Konishi Battalion's
frontline commander, Kikkawa Genshin.
State your rank and name.
Well, my rank is dog.
- His rank is dog.
- My name…
- And his name is…
- I answer to Bastard.
It's Bastard.
"Yi Jong-ryeo"?
You are quite skilled
for a Joseon swordsman.
A skilled swordsman
is a rarity in Joseon.
Well, you're not so bad yourself, are you?
You are quite skilled.
- Losing strength already?
- Tired already?
I just haven't eaten all day is all.
How about you give me one
of those rice balls first?
He says he's hungry.
He wants some rice balls.
Are you unharmed?
Once I get off this boat…
destroy the dock.
But, sire, if we destroy the dock,
the people will have no means of refuge.
This boat too. Sink it as well.
Don't leave anything the enemy
could use for rafts, understand?
Set fire to all the homes.
Burn everything down.
STRUGGLE
7 YEARS LATER
Hey, give it here!
Hogging all the food for yourself?
I want some too!
No, it's mine! Mine!
- What's this? Is it food?
- It's a corpse. A dead body.
Leave us a leg at least, please?
It is I, Gwang-yi.
I found two this time.
Cheon-yeong's still missing.
I will keep searching, sir.
SUNCHEON BASE CAMP OF THE RIGHTEOUS ARMY
(VOLUNTEER MILITIA)
Please.
I'm sorry I couldn't have done more.
General Kim, I wish you
good health and longevity.
That's… Raise your heads.
That's… that's enough.
Thanks to you, General,
we can go home safely.
- I owe it all to you, friends.
- No, not at all.
Hey, Beom-dong,
why the long face?
Do you really think it's a good idea
to let 'em go home like this?
They say some Japanese rats are
still roaming around disguised as locals.
I think everyone's tired.
We've been fighting for years now.
It's time to move on, isn't it?
♪ Hurrah, how exciting ♪
♪ Just live and let live
Just live and let live… ♪
Here.
They all get to go home now,
but we have to stay behind
and clean up the mess. Is that it?
- Ugh.
- Oh! Look who it is!
Mr. Tactician!
I hope he brought some good news
this time around.
I appreciate
all your efforts.
- How long has it been?
- Too long.
You see, I had a dream last night,
and in it, the pond in the garden
looked three times bigger.
What a sight to behold.
Truly it was.
Eh, brush.
A pavilion.
I want to build a larger pavilion here,
like in the dream.
And, son, would you want to be
the one who names it?
Father, I'm not…
I do not understand
why we're rushing to rebuild.
Surely the palace can wait.
Look at this.
The character for "palace"
combines the characters
for "spine" and "roof."
Without the palace to represent
the strength of this country,
sovereign rule is just an idea.
This represents real power!
You think you can attain real power
through ideas alone?
- 600 rooms, you say?
- Sire.
600 is lacking, I think.
6,000 sounds a little more fitting, I say.
Quite right.
KING SEONJO'S TEMPORARY RESIDENCE
Uh…
Uh.
All of you sacrificed so much
for the crown during the war.
It's a pleasure to have you here today.
We are truly obliged, Your Majesty.
We are truly obliged.
Begin the feast, I say.
Wow!
Now this is a feast, isn't it?
All the corpses laying around
mean we get fat crows!
- It's cooked to perfection.
- Thank you.
I'm about to pass out.
All right, now, let's see here.
Ah… Ah…
That's not…
That's right.
Once a nobleman, always a nobleman.
Enough of all that. Just take a bite.
Or do you want me to come
and pick the meat for you?
Um…
You really had to put me on the spot.
How was that?
Eat up.
Goddamn, this is bad.
General, about how many Japanese
have we killed at this point?
What's going on?
Aren't they supposed
to allow us our freedom
for our contributions to the war effort?
Bastards couldn't keep their word
if their necks depended on it.
What's the explanation this go around?
"The royal court can't approve it
at this time."
"Your victories can't be verified
without proof."
They have many.
I plan
to visit Hanyang soon,
and I'll request an audience
with the king.
I understand how you all feel, but please,
just a little longer is all I ask.
General,
instead of wasting your time and energy
going all the way to see the king,
let's just settle down here.
I mean, we can build a village right here.
And build a community. All of us together.
How does that sound to you?
General, I heard you sold your mansion
and everything you had
to fight for your country.
We can build you an even bigger mansion.
We got a roofer right here.
And where's the carpenter?
- Right here!
- Look, there we go. We're all set!
So then, how many rooms are you thinking?
For your…
Did I not make myself clear, General?
One for us all.
Oh my goodness.
It was your slave, you said?
He was the one
who killed your entire family?
I treated him as an equal
and took care of him,
but he kept running away,
so then my family hired hunters.
He was dragged back one day,
and he swore to burn my family alive,
and that's how they died,
just the way he said.
Awful, awful.
However,
I can't exactly say
you are completely free from blame.
What compelled you
to treat a slave like an equal?
You know Jeong Yeo-rip, yes?
And his "Great Unity"
or whatever he called it.
It wasn't that, sire. I simply…
I know.
I understand.
But even if you grow fond of the lowborn,
you must learn to hide those feelings.
Favoritism tends to breed arrogance
in them.
Benevolence will beget chaos
within their kind.
Such is the harsh
and often terrible burden
of we who rule, you see.
Drink up.
I, too, experienced such an immense loss
during the war.
So how could I not sympathize?
Our people experienced untold horrors
during the war,
but nothing compares
to what you went through, sire.
We must restore the palace quickly
to ensure your safety.
- This is our priority.
- Oh.
Your Majesty.
The war wreaked havoc on our country
for seven years.
Our constituents are resorting to eating
the flesh off of their dead to survive.
How can such starved, ill people
handle the massive effort
of constructing an entire palace?
Not only that,
scores of citizens lost their noses
to the savagery of the Japanese.
That was due to
Toyotomi Hideyoshi's bounty, was it not?
It sounds like you blame me? And besides…
- You don't need a nose to lift.
- Your Majesty!
First, form an agency of recognition
to honor those who contributed
to our victory.
Then raise the lowborn status of those
who fought with everything they had.
This will win back the hearts
of the people, Your Majesty.
There's no need for tears.
Agency of recognition, very well.
Do as you will.
I never told you you couldn't, did I?
However, the palace restoration
cannot be delayed any further.
Establish a separate agency
for that as well.
Understood?
Head!
Hold on. One moment.
- Let go of me!
- What, you don't think I know your tricks?
Oh my!
Sh!
Sh, sh, sh, sh!
All right, then.
You must follow proper decorum.
You know this.
You're a noble.
You can't treat a lowborn as a friend.
I…
So I can show affection to a dog,
but it's not allowed with a lowborn?
A dog is raised,
while a slave is meant to be commanded.
Goodness.
Understood.
I shall go command my slave, then.
Let's hurry. Hurry.
- It's hot even at dawn.
- Shut up and keep walking.
General!
General! Japanese soldiers are here!
Beom-dong! Hyung-nim! Come quickly!
I'm telling you,
I saw Japanese invaders in disguise!
Here and here.
They're bound to reveal themselves
if we cut off their means of escape.
The king's palace, uh…
is it in that direction?
Isn't it over there?
The direction of the Rat.
RAT
Must we do this
every time we head to battle?
If anything, the king should be the one
doing the bowing.
General! I think we found it.
Sir.
We got it! Bullseye!
It's an ambush! Ambush!
Arms out! To battle!
Here's what I think.
- We don't kill them all.
- Oh, you're dead!
I guess that's that.
Shall we, then? Let's go!
No. No!
He… he's here! The blue-robed god!
General!
Look who we have here.
I have been wondering
who the blue-robed god could be.
You're the blue-robed god?
That scar I gave you
is pretty distinctive, isn't it?
Looks real nice. Want another one?
Your other cheek looks lonely.
He says he could give you
the same pretty scar on the other side.
Sure. Why not?
You are still such a joker.
Have you eaten?
You're not hungry, are you?
- He's asking if you've eaten.
- Well, no.
I never eat breakfast!
You son of a…
Bastards!
You bastards!
You little rat!
What the…
Ha!
Chujo-ryu?
Thanks to me,
soon you'll be able to see your nose
even without a mirror!
Hmm? Hmm?
- General!
- We must get out of here!
They've got us…
- Do not interfere.
- This is a duel between us.
He wants a duel with you.
Cheon-yeong!
You're still fighting, really?
Do you know how long ago we finished?
It's all under control.
I'll end this right now.
Sounds like they beat our men.
The general said
to capture them alive. Got it?
It doesn't sound
like they'll kill us.
- Does he mean it?
- What?
He wants the king to see them.
Proof of our victory and whatnot.
Remember, we need to take them alive.
I mean, that's the only way
we're getting paid or freed.
This gonna take long?
No, you can just sit there
and watch the show.
They'll use us as bait
to strike a deal with the king.
Never mind.
Just give him the net.
No, don't do it!
What the hell is this?
- Call yourself a warrior?
- What's he saying?
Uh…
He's upset that the duel wasn't… um…
- Goddamnit.
- Sheesh.
I was just about to get in there
and end it with a powerful blow.
So this is
the infamous Nose Snatcher.
It's the goblin helmet.
Wait, we just caught the Nose Snatcher?
The Nose Snatcher?!
The devil that'll cut
your nose off while you're still alive?
Look at this gold!
We can build ourselves a village
with all this.
- Whoa.
- The rumors are true.
The Japanese remnants
have squirreled away treasure.
Really?
Let me have a look.
Huh, not bad.
I will deliver this to the king.
Let's put it all back, then.
What?
Our duty now
is to deliver this gold to Hanyang.
The royal court will return these
to their rightful owners.
- Rightful, my ass.
- Hey, hey.
Beom-dong, where are you going?
- Water. Water!
- Me first!
So you're the famous Nose Snatcher?
Are you the Nose Snatcher?
How could you do this?
He wants water too.
And I wanted a rice ball seven years ago.
He said
you didn't give him rice balls, remember?
On about rice again?
You knew the Chujo-ryu technique.
Who taught you?
- What is he saying?
- Huh?
The short sword technique.
My lord wonders
who taught you the short sword technique.
Someone in Namwon
with a rabbit-shaped helmet.
Someone who was wearing
a hare-shaped helmet in Namwon.
Friend of yours?
His technique was interesting,
so I took it.
His technique was…
You just picked it up?
Mm-hmm.
He learned it
while fighting.
When I plunged my sword
into his stomach,
everything inside just gushed out.
He cut his stomach open,
and his intestines gushed out.
I would like a rematch.
He says he wants another duel.
The outcome will be no different.
The outcome won't change.
Go ahead and kill me, then…
like a true warrior!
He says, in that case, he'd rather die.
Unfortunately, I still need you alive.
So just sit tight and look pretty.
He said he has a use for you.
What is it you are hiding
underneath that red cloth?
He wants to know
what you're protecting on your hand.
You got scarred while you were training.
So that, from now on,
you'll always remember
why you came in first.
Being offered a position
in the Royal Guard
so soon after your exam.
I came to talk
about Cheon-yeong's release.
I started as a guard
just like your grandfather before me.
I worked the border regions
for many years.
I underwent many hardships.
- Father, please.
- The elders are waiting. Let us go.
You gave him your word. You promised!
How embarrassing.
Are you letting that slave rub off on you?
He brought home the royal flowers, Father.
How can you go back on your word?
Cheon-yeong kept his word as a slave,
and now you, as a noble, can't--
You fool!
We would both be dead right now
if the king learned
that your test results were fabricated.
Cheon-yeong's already…
all prepared to leave.
Very well.
Gwang-yi must be ready by now as well.
Celebrate!
Where is that rat?
- He's not here.
- Gwang-yi, you bastard!
We were told to catch him,
but we don't have to bring him back alive.
Master's orders.
Just try it.
And I'll cut your arm right off
at the shoulder.
Then I shall bring him back.
Cheon… Cheon-yeong.
You said you'd bring my papers.
Where are they?
Thank God you're safe.
I was so worried, Cheon-yeong.
Run away.
Go fight the Mongols
at the northern border,
or go to the south and fight pirates.
I heard slaves
sometimes get freed after enlisting.
- Make sure you don't get captured--
- Listen.
Am I still your friend?
Yes.
Oh, oh.
So you're saying these are all appeals
requesting that Kim Ja-ryeong
and his squadron
get recognized for their achievements?
Across the country, I hear it said,
"Sun-sin protects our seas,
while Ja-ryeong protects our lands."
Ah. Hmm.
But then, Admiral Sun-sin
died for his country.
Ja-ryeong did not.
And not a single report
on the construction of the palace is here,
is it?
The Palace Construction
Agency created a budget
and estimated
the number of workers necessary,
and concluded that it is not something
we can afford presently.
I'm sorry, kid.
Look at that perfect posture!
That's great!
Beautiful!
Now that's some ugly fucking hair.
Looks Japanese, doesn't it?
These greedy pigs make me sick.
Thank you.
The people who actually fought the enemy
have to gnaw on corpses
just to stay alive.
But the ones who got
in bed with the enemy,
they're feasting on ribs
and having the time of their lives.
"Meat is meat, either way." Is that it?
This cannot stand.
The mayor of Cheongju is a traitor.
- We must inform His Majesty.
- And that'll do what?
No, not even gouging out his throat
will be good enough.
Hey, Cheon-yeong!
- You better be kidding.
- We have a long road ahead.
I don't wanna argue.
I'd rather get some sleep.
Well, in that case…
let's all just part here.
To tell you the truth,
I get sick of you going on and on
all the time about "His Majesty,"
and I can't stand to be around someone
who cares as little as you do!
Well, it's not as though we were planning
on sticking together forever.
Let's just give up
and go back where we belong.
Right.
Go back to where we belong.
Yes, fine.
Hope you get your freedom, then.
While you're at it, get a title too.
Have a nice life.
While it is true
that the court once lost its way,
the seven-year war has run its course.
And with the talented Crown Prince,
I'm certain the court
will regain its dignity.
We must trust the government
to reward the just
and to punish the unjust!
I can't! It's killing me!
I feel like I can't breathe!
I can't do this anymore!
This is why the idea of harmony,
that we could all live together,
regardless of birthrights and class,
is… just a dream.
Even so, General…
…in all my life, I've only met
one true nobleman.
Thank you for everything, General.
I wish you good health.
The Nose Snatcher is ours!
All that's left to do to get our freedom
is to bring him to the court!
What's gotten into all of you?
It's absurd to quit now!
Beom-dong!
- Let's go.
- Hey, let's go. Everyone get up.
Cheon-yeong, take care of the general.
An internal conflict has erupted.
Mr. Tactician!
Damn, it looks even worse up close.
- Huh?
- Yeah, it's Japanese as hell.
What'd I say? I told you so.
We should leave one sack
in front of each home.
First time having rice in years,
I'd imagine.
- We should eat up first.
- Ah, right.
- Wow, that looks delicious.
- Here, I brought some more.
- Can't remember the last time I ate rice.
- I can't either.
Don't you know who I am?!
I am the mayor of Cheongju,
appointed by His Majesty himself.
Where are your Confucian virtues?
I say you're just ignorant beasts!
Confucian virtues?
The only virtues I know of…
are those of the flail.
WEST GATE, HANYANG
General Kim Ja-ryeong is here!
- Oh, we were so worried for you.
- Yes, yes, thank you so much.
Get off me!
Please, the corrupt officials
are even worse than the Japanese!
We starve, yet they work us like dogs
to rebuild the palace!
I will relay all your worries
to the king myself, so just
a little patience is all I ask.
Ja-ryeong's won the hearts
of the populace, it seems.
Don't you agree?
You would think he's a Ming emperor.
Such enthusiastic cheers
for a mere general.
How does this hero's welcome sit with you?
The ignorant masses are easily swayed
by absurd tales of grandeur,
but the truth will be revealed.
Your Majesty need not be concerned by it.
What is it?
A letter
from the Chungcheong district inspector.
I was told it was an urgent matter.
The Cheongju mayor was killed
a few days ago.
Word has it
that it was Kim Ja-ryeong's people.
What is it?
- Step back!
- Everyone be silent!
Step back!
General Kim, His Majesty
requests a private audience with you.
Huh.
I don't think His Majesty
would appreciate my smell.
Ah, right.
I know he'll ask your name
as it's written.
Which "Cheon" and which "young"
should I say you use to write it?
It doesn't matter.
It no longer has any meaning.
I think "sky" and "brilliant,"
like "shining."
That's what I would have picked
were I your father.
We'll speak later.
We have meat and liquor
prepared for all of you.
You must be famished
after that long journey. Follow me.
Let's go have some meat!
Quickly!
It isn't as though Ja-ryeong
himself killed the Cheongju mayor.
However, he led them for seven years.
That cannot be.
Ja-ryeong is a Confucian scholar.
I do not see him
as such an ignorant scoundrel.
I want him brought here
so I can question him myself.
By the king's command,
seize the traitorous rebel Kim Ja-ryeong!
- Huh?
What?
I thought we were having a feast.
What? What?
They're all guilty of treason.
Death upon the traitorous bastards!
Rebellion.
I used the blunt edge of my sword
to not kill any of the king's guards.
Do you understand?
Now tell the king
General Kim Ja-ryeong
formally requests an audience.
What are you waiting for?
Seize him!
After him!
You are obliged to speak.
My body rages with a burning fire.
There's no way to tame it,
so I keep my mouth shut.
Burning, you say?
Were you chewing a pepper?
Where did your virtue go?
Did it meet the same fate as your palace
and turn to ash?
Did you hear that?
Even this traitor agrees
the Confucian virtues dictate,
a palace is necessary
for a king to rule unimpeded.
Spoken like a true Confucian scholar.
Beom-dong, you…
you never even learned to read,
yet… you read this world clear as day.
- Oh my goodness.
- The general, a traitor?
I can't believe this.
Well, the years have certainly flown by,
haven't they?
Cheon-yeong has returned
to greet his young master.
Even a dog in a brothel gets to eat rice
if he jumps up and catches a thief,
doesn't he?
Yet Our Majesty,
who promised us freedom and honor,
frames us and kills us.
Like your father,
he stabbed us in the back.
A dog that bites has to be put down.
Still, I'd hoped you'd turn out different,
Jong-ryeo.
You traitor!
How dare you speak of betrayal, huh?
Ah!
Aah!
I was a fool for ever befriending you
like I did.
For that, I resent myself.
Not my problem.
I should have just…
just raised a dog instead.
There it is.
You sure
that's not just your wife talking?
Cheon-yeong, you animal!
- Over there!
- Hurry!
Branded a traitor by the Kingdom,
so then a traitor I shall be.
Hurry!
After him! There!
TRAITOR JEONG YEO-RIP OK-NAM,
SON OF THE TRAITOR JEONG YEO-RIP
The heads that were hanging
are gone!
REVOLT
I executed Ja-ryeong,
following your loyal advice.
Now I'm drowning in appeals.
Thousands are calling on me
to right this wrong.
They hold you responsible for this.
Riots are breaking out
all over the country.
What am I to do?
Oh!
How absolutely exquisite.
This was found in Joseon,
completely untouched?
According to the Nose Snatcher,
the Japanese remnants were planning
to bring the treasure here in chests
to offer them as gifts to you,
Your Majesty.
Treasure chests, you say?
If there's truly that much treasure, then…
We can sell it to traders
of Ming antiques.
And raise the funds necessary
for the restoration of…
Tell me, where…
where is this treasure, hmm?
Where?
I AM YI JONG-RYEO
OF THE ROYAL INVESTIGATION BUREAU
Yi Jong-ryeo?
What is it that you want?
The blue-robed god.
Why don't we use the surrendered Japanese
for this?
We bring them into our ranks
and have them search in secret.
Hmm.
The councilors would never
let me hear the end of it, would they?
If we say the Japanese remnants
are there to quell the riots…
Two birds with one stone.
We can suppress the civil uprising
while simultaneously finding the treasure.
And what remains of Ja-ryeong's followers
will be completely wiped out.
The surrendered general
will be allowed to lead a unit
of the remaining Japanese
and will henceforth be known
as Kim Choong-myeon.
Your Majesty! I say the Japanese general
should be beheaded immediately, my lord.
Yet you'll have him kill more of our own?
I beg you reconsider, sire.
We beg you reconsider, sire.
They burned down the palace.
They even attempted
to murder their own king.
Subjects, huh?
They're not even human, I say!
In the past, I established a military unit
made up solely
of surrendered Japanese soldiers.
At first, the people had doubts,
but my reasoning was sound.
Choong-myeon is now my loyal subject,
so his past is now irrelevant.
Furthermore, Yi Jong-ryeo
of the Investigation Bureau,
I appoint you Chief of Punitive Forces.
You will lead the newly formed unit
to take down the traitors.
You will bring swift justice
upon them all.
I, Yi Jong-ryeo,
am grateful for this chance
to serve Your Majesty
and to rebuild our great nation.
Huh? Hey, hyung-nim.
Hyung-nim!
What happened to you?
Thought you'd be a king's guard by now.
What happened to you? You're a mess.
Whoa, hyung-nim!
Hey. Hey!
What did I say, huh?
What did I tell you?!
I told you not to go there!
Did I not?! What did I tell you?!
Let go!
- Enough.
- What did I say?!
I told you they were full of shit!
All so that you could live a better life.
- I said enough.
- Look where it got you, huh?!
Look what you did!
Look at what you've done!
There, there.
Hey, Cheon-yeong, get up.
- I wanna have a duel.
- Just talk it out.
Hey, come on now!
Now what the fuck is that?!
- You gotta honor the king first, really?
- Enough!
RAT
Let this be the end of it.
You can fight in a war
and come home a hero,
but if you rebel,
there's a chance you might not come back.
Whether by Japanese swords
or under the blade of the king,
it's all the same thing.
Plus, how can we pull off a revolution
when there's only 30 of us here?
Come on, it's simple.
Our homeland is falling apart.
Put up a damn poster.
We'll have more here than we can count.
How will we feed and clothe them, then?
Wait, you said it yourself, sir.
The Japanese forces have buried treasure.
Wait a minute.
When we caught the Nose Snatcher,
the rats had these big empty wagons.
What's the point of hauling them
all the way out to the woods unless…
They were gonna use them
to move the hidden treasure.
Come to think of it, there were marks
on some of the older trees.
That's right. Remember?
Of course. Yes. Let's check it out.
The key to a revolution is speed.
We need to hurry.
- Here. I think this was the spot.
- Here.
Look, there it is!
Careful, careful, careful.
Let's see, let's see!
- Whoa.
- We did it.
We found the treasure!
We need
at least two more wagons.
And where are we gonna find those?
Let's pull the rest on horseback.
Yeah, I guess we could do that.
I don't think it's anything
you need to concern yourselves with.
- What's going on?
- What are you doing?
Have you lost your damn minds?
You think we're Japanese or something?!
Stay still, dammit!
If bringing change to this nation
is worth risking your life,
stand over there.
But if you wish to take this treasure
and split it among us,
then stand over here.
After fighting for more than seven years,
what did it all mean?
If you want to live free,
then grab your belongings
and come to me.
That's not freedom!
If you truly want freedom,
it's gotta be won.
We can't afford to stop.
If we do, they'll keep coming.
We'll be targets forever!
Until we end up dead!
I don't wanna hear this drivel.
If you want me to bash your head in,
then by all means, stand over there.
Are you serious? What are you doing?
I just… Tomorrow is never guaranteed,
so I'm gonna appreciate today.
You disgust me.
Kim Ja-ryeong sees what you're doing
from his grave!
Now come on! Let's load it all up
and get outta here.
- Beom-dong noo-nim!
- Let's go. Come on.
He doesn't wanna go with you.
Let him go, at least. Kid!
Eyes ahead.
Do you want to go back?
- Mm-hmm.
- It's certain death.
Mm-hmm. Please.
Hurry then,
before a hungry boar finds them.
Good luck, kid.
♪ I want to live ♪
♪ Hurrah, hurrah, how exciting ♪
♪ I want to live in a big mansion ♪
♪ Hurrah, how exciting ♪
♪ I want to eat, I want to eat ♪
♪ I want to eat a royal meal ♪
♪ Hurrah, how exciting ♪
What?
Your commander, Cheon-yeong?
The Nose Snatcher? How could he…
We're sending a message here.
Cut off their heads.
Huh?
Hey, Kiddo. You came back.
What happened here? What the hell is this?
Mr. Tactician.
You should have just… died at my hands.
WANTED
"I will hang heads and wait."
"Yi Jong-ryeo."
- Take it over there. Good.
- Make sure it's tied tight.
The boat should be arriving at low tide.
Until then, the unit will stand guard here
while another contingent
searches for the rebels.
Yes, sir.
How dare they!
I'll kill them all, I swear.
Wait a minute.
Something seems off.
What the…
Oh, I see.
We, too, are a military unit
that receives His Majesty's commands.
Do you intend to commit treason too?
What you're doing
is treasonous. The king selected--
You were never going
to get out of here alive.
You're the enemy, you see.
He never planned
to let us leave.
You'll make
for a good, hearty meal.
We'll flay your meat
and sleep in your leather.
Fire!
If the barrel is backed up,
the weapon will explode.
Doesn't it remind you of this country?
Swords out!
What on earth is going on?
What a load of bullshit.
Aah!
In the fog, we'll be blinded.
I don't think we can set sail
at this rate.
We are in no rush.
- Sir!
- General.
You and the blue-robed god.
You two are so different
yet mirror images at a certain angle.
What exactly are you to each other,
you and he?
What's your relationship
with the blue-robed god?
You're the same, and yet…
and yet you're different.
The anger
in your sword is different from his.
So why does he… Why did
the blue-robed god have your sword?
Did he steal it?
Did the blue-robed god
steal your sword?
I gave it willingly.
He says he gave it to him.
I will not kill you.
You'll be valuable
when it comes to negotiations.
You'll be more useful to us
as a bargaining chip than dead,
so my lord will not kill you.
You're both
of the same kind.
I will treat you… equally.
It's the blue-robed god!
The blue-robed god.
I have a use for him,
so be nice and keep him alive.
He has a use for him,
so my lord wants you to keep him alive.
I'll just kill you both.
Bring… bring me my foot.
Oh fuck, I'm…
Are you all right, sir?
You little shit!
Sh…
Got you!
You lowly bitch!
Don't cry over a scratch.
Not when others died
with their heads cut off.
And some burned to death.
I'll rip your limbs off
and tear you to shreds,
and I'll take all of those pieces
and burn them away.
This is for my father!
My mother, my son!
As my wife suffered, so shall you!
Is that what you thought
happened all along?
Or is that something you chose to believe?
I really tried to save them,
but she willingly jumped
into the raging fire
with your son in her arms.
You liar!
That's a goddamn lie!
Why would she?
Why?!
And she said I was a brute at the end.
I'm getting tired of waiting.
Cheon-yeong.
Am I still…
still your friend?
Cheon-yeong, I'm…
so sorry.
Jong-ryeo.
Ah, it is exactly how I envisioned it.
Just like in my dream. Hmm.
- Now what about…
- Ah, yes, Your Majesty?
The pine trees on Namsan, then.
Is it done?
Uh… Well, you see…
The trees hold a lot of moisture
in the summer, so…
Mm! Tsk!
- It is I, Eunuch Kim.
- Enter.
I was told that a cargo vessel
arrived at Hangangjin, sire.
It bears the royal insignia and…
Is Jong-ryeo still nowhere to be found?
They searched every part of the vessel,
but there was no sign he was there.
Are you saying the ship
sailed here on its own?
The entire unit disappearing
with no witnesses… It makes no sense.
Oh!
Excellent.
Hurry up and open them.
Why is this taking so long?
Over here! This one's open, sire.
Oh! The rest of you, keep going.
Sire!
All right, open it.
Huh? What does this salt mean?
- My lord, this one is open!
- This one too.
- We opened ours too.
- We got this one!
- We got it open!
- This one is also open!
- Jab and pull it out.
- Sire.
Just push it on its side.
Hmm?
Huh?
What?
Aah!
- Your Majesty!
- Oh! Ah!
Your Majesty.
CHAOS
KING
Attention!
To punish those who leech off the people,
we must all join forces!
That's right!
Just like this strong, fearsome brute!
Hey!
Here, eat him up!
The characters for the word
"brute" are the same
as the ones used for "the masses."
That's true.
Since the masses are beasts,
it is only right that they fear us!
No better way to join forces
than to form a community.
I think we should give ourselves
a new name
since the Great Unity didn't work out.
Beom-dong works, doesn't it?
"A world together," meaning all of us.
Beom… dong.
Those characters fit perfectly.
Does that mean
I'm the boss, then?
Do we really need a boss?
Let's have some fun! Whoo!
Sounds good. Let's do it!